0	0	1999-09-23	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
0	1	22	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	09	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	ALL	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Money
1	1	BUDGETED	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	2	STORIES	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	3	HAVE	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	4	MOVED	VBD	O	B-VP	O
1	5	except	IN	O	O	O
1	6	:	:	O	O	O
1	7	MUSEUM-GIULIANI-ASSESS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	9	NY-PHILHARMONIC-REVIEW	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
1	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	11	BANDITS-FILM-REVIEW	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
1	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	13	LEHMAN-EARNINGS	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
1	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	15	BAUER-ECON	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
1	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	17	BBO-AUCTION	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	18	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
1	19	BBA-YANKS-CHISOX	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	20	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	Recapping	VBG	O	O	O
2	1	:	:	O	O	O

3	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	1	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
3	2	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	3	eliminated	VBN	O	I-VP	O
3	4	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	5	tonight	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	6	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
3	7	NYTNS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	8	budgets	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	9	:	:	O	O	O

4	0	TOBACCO-SUIT	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
4	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

5	0	KIRKLAND-MEMORIAL	NNP	O	O	O
5	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
5	2	Washington	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
5	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

6	0	TAIWAN-AID	NNP	O	O	O

7	0	N.Y.	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	1	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	2	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	3	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	4	.	.	O	O	O
