0	0	1999-09-23	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	20	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	52	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	JOHN	NNP	O	I-NP	O
0	5	AND	CC	O	I-NP	O
0	6	JANE	NNP	O	I-NP	O
0	7	DOE	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Animal
0	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
0	9	CHOOSE	NNP	O	O	O
0	10	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
0	11	MODEL	NNP	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
0	12	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
0	13	FOR	IN	O	B-PP	O
0	14	RELEASE	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
0	15	SUNDAY	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
0	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
0	17	SEPT.	NNP	O	O	O
0	18	26	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	19	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

1	0	Names	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	2	like	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	3	wolves	NNS	O	B-NP	B-Animal
1	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	5	run	VBP	O	B-VP	O
1	6	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	7	packs	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	8	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	People	NNS	O	B-NP	O
2	1	who	WP	O	B-NP	O
2	2	keep	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	3	tabs	NNS	O	B-NP	O
2	4	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	5	newborns	NNS	O	B-NP	O
2	6	say	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	7	that	IN	O	O	O
2	8	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	9	lot	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	11	Pampers	NNPS	O	B-NP	O
2	12	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	13	currently	RB	O	I-VP	O
2	14	wrapped	VBN	O	I-VP	O
2	15	around	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	16	Michaels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
2	17	and	CC	O	O	O
2	18	Jessicas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
2	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	20	not	RB	O	O	O
2	21	to	TO	O	O	O
2	22	mention	VB	O	O	O
2	23	Jacobs	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
2	24	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
2	25	Samanthas	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
2	26	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	1	automotive	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	2	equivalent	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	3	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	4	``	``	O	O	O
3	5	LS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	6	.	.	O	O	O
3	7	''	''	O	O	O

4	0	If	IN	O	O	O
4	1	that	IN	O	B-NP	O
4	2	doesn	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	3	't	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	4	dance	VB	O	B-VP	O
4	5	off	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	7	tongue	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	9	you	PRP	O	B-NP	O
4	10	can	MD	O	B-VP	O
4	11	blame	VB	O	I-VP	O
4	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	13	Europeans	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
4	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	15	whose	WP$	O	B-NP	O
4	16	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	17	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	18	alphanumeric	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	19	names	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	20	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	21	lieu	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	22	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	23	animals	NNS	O	B-NP	B-Animal
4	24	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	25	Mustang	NNP	O	O	B-Animal
4	26	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	28	evocative	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	29	places	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	30	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	31	Yukon	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
4	32	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	33	and	CC	O	O	O
4	34	coined	VBD	O	O	O
4	35	words	NNS	O	B-NP	O
4	36	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	37	Vitara	NNP	O	O	O
4	38	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	39	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	40	spread	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	41	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
4	42	auto	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	43	makers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	44	elsewhere	RB	O	O	O
4	45	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	Lincoln	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	1	named	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	2	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	3	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
5	4	luxury	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	5	car	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	6	the	DT	O	I-NP	O
5	7	LS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	8	because	IN	O	O	O
5	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	10	L	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	11	stands	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
5	12	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	13	luxury	NN	O	B-NP	O
5	14	and	CC	O	O	O
5	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	16	S	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	17	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	18	sport	NN	O	B-NP	O
5	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	20	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	21	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	22	spokesman	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	24	Jim	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	25	Trainor	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
5	26	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	Also	RB	O	O	O
6	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	3	car	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	4	competes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	5	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	6	European	JJ	O	B-NP	B-LangRace
6	7	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
6	8	Japanese	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
6	9	autos	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	10	that	IN	O	B-NP	O
6	11	typically	RB	O	B-VP	O
6	12	use	VBP	O	I-VP	O
6	13	alphanumeric	JJ	O	B-NP	O
6	14	names	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	16	like	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	18	BMW	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
6	19	528i	NN	O	I-NP	B-Num
6	20	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Saturn	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	1	Corp.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
7	2	says	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	3	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
7	4	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
7	5	LS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	6	stands	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	7	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	8	large	JJ	O	B-NP	O
7	9	sedan	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	10	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	11	although	IN	O	O	O
7	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	13	car	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	14	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	15	actually	RB	O	I-VP	O
7	16	classified	VBN	O	I-VP	O
7	17	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	18	midsized	JJ	O	O	O
7	19	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	Some	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	1	other	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	2	auto	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	3	makers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	4	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	5	less	RBR	O	O	O
8	6	specific	NN	O	O	O
8	7	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	8	why	WRB	O	O	O
8	9	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
8	10	use	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	12	name	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	13	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	Chevrolet	NNP	O	B-NP	O
9	1	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
9	2	LS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
9	3	versions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	4	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	5	its	PP$	O	O	O
9	6	Cavalier	NNP	O	O	O
9	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	8	Malibu	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
9	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	10	Impala	NNP	O	O	B-Animal
9	11	and	CC	O	O	O
9	12	Monte	NNP	O	B-NP	O
9	13	Carlo	NNP	O	I-NP	O
9	14	cars	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	15	;	:	O	O	O
9	16	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
9	17	Silverado	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
9	18	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
9	19	S-10	NNP	O	I-NP	O
9	20	pickups	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	21	;	:	O	O	O
9	22	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
9	23	Astro	NNP	O	I-NP	O
9	24	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
9	25	Express	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
9	26	and	CC	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	27	Venture	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	28	vans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	29	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	30	and	CC	O	O	O
9	31	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
9	32	Blazer	NNP	O	I-NP	O
9	33	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
9	34	Tahoe	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
9	35	utilities	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	36	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	Dan	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
10	1	Hubbard	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
10	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	3	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	4	Chevrolet	NNP	O	I-NP	O
10	5	spokesman	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	7	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	9	L	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	10	originally	RB	O	O	O
10	11	denoted	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	12	luxury	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	13	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	But	CC	O	O	O
11	1	Chevy	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
11	2	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
11	3	consumer	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	4	studies	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	5	found	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	6	that	IN	O	O	O
11	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	8	second	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
11	9	letter	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	10	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	11	even	RB	O	O	O
11	12	more	RBR	O	O	O
11	13	important	JJ	O	O	O
11	14	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	``	``	O	O	O
12	1	Our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
12	2	research	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	3	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
12	4	shown	VBN	O	I-VP	O
12	5	that	IN	O	O	O
12	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	7	farther	RB	O	I-NP	O
12	8	up	IN	O	O	O
12	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	11	alphabet	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	12	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
12	13	go	VBP	O	B-VP	O
12	14	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	15	letters	NNS	O	B-NP	O
12	16	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
12	17	follow	VB	O	I-VP	O
12	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	19	L	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	20	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	21	people	NNS	O	B-NP	O
12	22	think	VBP	O	B-VP	O
12	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	24	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	25	vehicle	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	26	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	27	being	VBG	O	B-VP	O
12	28	more	JJR	O	B-NP	O
12	29	upscaleCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	30	''	''	O	O	O
12	31	Hubbard	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
12	32	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	33	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	To	TO	O	B-PP	O
13	1	that	DT	O	O	O
13	2	end	VBP	O	B-VP	O
13	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	4	top-line	JJ	O	B-NP	O
13	5	Chevrolet	NNP	O	I-NP	O
13	6	trucks	NNS	O	I-NP	O
13	7	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	8	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	9	step	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	10	up	IN	O	O	O
13	11	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	13	LS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
13	14	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	15	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
13	16	LTs	NNP	O	B-NP	O
13	17	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	Mercury	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
14	1	sells	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
14	2	LS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	3	versions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	4	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	5	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
14	6	Tracer	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
14	8	Mystique	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
14	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
14	10	Sable	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
14	11	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
14	12	Grand	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
14	13	Marquis	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
14	14	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	1	Sable	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
15	2	competitor	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	5	Buick	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
15	6	Regal	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
15	8	also	RB	O	O	I-Org
15	9	comes	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
15	10	in	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
15	11	LS	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	12	form	VBP	O	B-VP	I-Org
15	13	_	NN	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	14	but	CC	O	O	I-Org
15	15	that	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	16	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
15	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	18	plainest	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	19	Regal	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	20	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
15	21	whereas	IN	O	O	I-Org
15	22	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	23	LS	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	24	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
15	25	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
15	26	fanciest	JJS	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	27	Sable	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	28	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	1	base	VBP	O	I-NP	O
16	2	Sable	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
16	3	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
16	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	5	GS	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	7	as	IN	O	O	O
16	8	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
16	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	10	top	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	11	Regal	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	12	.	.	O	O	O
