0	0	1998-09-22	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	19	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	33	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	RUSSIA	NNP	O	I-NP	O
0	5	OPPOSES	NNP	O	I-NP	O
0	6	KOSOVO	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
0	7	INTERVENTION	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
0	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
0	9	NEW	JJ	O	B-NP	O
0	10	FOREIGN	JJ	O	I-NP	O
0	11	MINISTER	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
0	12	SAYS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
0	13	AT	IN	O	B-PP	O
0	14	U.N	NNP	O	B-NP	O
0	15	.	.	O	O	O

1	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
1	1	JT	NNP	O	O	B-Org
1	2	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

2	0	UNITED	NNP	O	O	O
2	1	NATIONS	NNP	O	O	O
2	2	_	NN	O	O	O
2	3	Moscow	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
2	4	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
2	5	opposed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
2	6	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
2	7	any	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	8	efforts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	9	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
2	10	use	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	11	outside	IN	O	B-NP	O
2	12	force	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	13	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
2	14	end	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	16	war	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	17	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	19	Serbian	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
2	20	province	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	21	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	22	Kosovo	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
2	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	24	Russia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
2	25	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
2	26	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	27	foreign	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	28	minister	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	29	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	30	Tuesday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
2	31	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	32	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
2	33	first	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
2	34	speech	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	35	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
2	36	world	NN	O	B-NP	O
2	37	leaders	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	38	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	Igor	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	1	Ivanov	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	4	minister	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	6	also	RB	O	O	O
3	7	warned	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	8	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	10	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	11	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	12	military	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	13	force	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	14	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	15	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
3	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	17	and	CC	O	O	O
3	18	raised	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	20	possibility	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	21	that	IN	O	O	O
3	22	Russia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
3	23	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
3	24	argue	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	25	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	26	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	27	coming	VBG	O	I-NP	O
3	28	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	29	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	30	debate	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	31	that	IN	O	O	O
3	32	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	33	Iraqis	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
3	34	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
3	35	no	RB	O	O	O
3	36	longer	JJR	O	O	O
3	37	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	38	threat	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	39	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
3	40	their	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	41	neighbors	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	42	and	CC	O	O	O
3	43	therefore	RB	O	O	O
3	44	deserve	VBP	O	B-VP	O
3	45	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	46	relief	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	47	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	48	economic	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	49	sanctions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	50	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	Both	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	1	Iraq	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
4	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	3	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
4	4	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	5	ended	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	6	most	JJS	O	B-NP	O
4	7	cooperation	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	8	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	9	U.N.	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	10	arms	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	11	inspectors	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
4	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	13	and	CC	O	O	O
4	14	Kosovo	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	17	subject	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	18	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	19	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	20	resolution	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	21	proposed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
4	22	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	23	France	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
4	24	and	CC	O	O	O
4	25	Britain	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
4	26	that	WDT	O	B-NP	O
4	27	would	MD	O	B-VP	O
4	28	authorize	VB	O	I-VP	O
4	29	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	30	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	31	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	32	NATO	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	33	forces	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	34	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	35	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
4	36	urgent	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	37	matters	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	38	before	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	39	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	40	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
4	41	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
4	42	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	Diplomats	NNS	O	B-NP	O
5	1	involved	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	2	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	4	negotiations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	5	surrounding	VBG	O	B-VP	O
5	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	7	Kosovo	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	8	resolution	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	9	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
5	10	focused	VBN	O	I-VP	O
5	11	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	12	how	WRB	O	O	O
5	13	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
5	14	get	VB	O	I-VP	O
5	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	16	measure	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	17	through	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	19	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	20	without	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	21	provoking	VBG	O	B-VP	O
5	22	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	23	Russian	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
5	24	veto	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	25	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	1	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	2	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	3	former	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	4	deputy	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
6	5	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
6	6	Yevgeny	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	7	Primakov	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	10	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	11	Russian	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
6	12	prime	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
6	13	minister	NN	O	I-NP	I-ProfTitle
6	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	15	who	WP	O	B-NP	O
6	16	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	17	Western	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	18	diplomats	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	19	expect	VBP	O	B-VP	O
6	20	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
6	21	take	VB	O	I-VP	O
6	22	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	23	consistently	RB	O	I-NP	O
6	24	harder	JJR	O	I-NP	O
6	25	line	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	26	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	27	foreign	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Jour
6	28	policy	NN	O	I-NP	I-Jour
6	29	issues	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	30	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	31	importance	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	32	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
6	33	Moscow	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
6	34	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Primakov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	2	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	3	former	JJ	O	I-NP	O
7	4	foreign	JJ	O	I-NP	O
7	5	minister	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
7	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	7	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	8	had	VBN	O	I-VP	O
7	9	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	10	long	JJ	O	I-NP	O
7	11	relationship	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	12	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	13	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
7	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	15	and	CC	O	O	O
7	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	17	Russians	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-Org
7	18	consider	VBP	O	B-VP	O
7	19	themselves	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	20	indispensable	JJ	O	B-NP	O
7	21	players	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	22	there	EX	O	O	O
7	23	and	CC	O	O	O
7	24	go-betweens	NNS	O	B-NP	O
7	25	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	26	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
7	27	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
7	28	enemies	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	29	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	On	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	1	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	2	former	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	3	Yugoslavia	NN	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
8	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	5	Russians	NNPS	O	B-NP	B-LangRace
8	6	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	7	long	RB	O	I-VP	O
8	8	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
8	9	opposed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
8	10	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
8	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	12	intrusion	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	14	NATO	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
8	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	16	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
8	17	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
8	18	now	RB	O	I-VP	O
8	19	threatening	VBG	O	I-VP	O
8	20	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
8	21	intervene	VB	O	I-VP	O
8	22	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	24	forces	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	25	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	26	President	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
8	27	Slobodan	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
8	28	Milosevic	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	29	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	30	Yugoslavia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
8	31	carry	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	32	out	IN	O	O	O
8	33	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	34	increasingly	RB	O	I-NP	O
8	35	deadly	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	36	campaign	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	37	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	38	ethnic	JJ	O	B-NP	O
8	39	Albanian	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
8	40	separatists	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	41	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	1	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
9	2	speech	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	3	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
9	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	5	53rd	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
9	6	session	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	9	U.N.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
9	10	General	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	11	Assembly	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	12	Tuesday	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
9	14	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
9	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
9	16	a	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
9	17	53-year-old	JJ	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	18	career	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	19	foreign	JJ	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	20	ministry	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	21	official	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	22	who	WP	O	B-NP	I-Org
9	23	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
9	24	regarded	VBN	O	I-VP	I-Org
9	25	as	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
9	26	a	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
9	27	loyal	JJ	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	28	Primakov	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	29	associate	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
9	30	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	31	spoke	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	32	out	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	33	generally	RB	O	O	O
9	34	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	35	military	JJ	O	B-NP	O
9	36	solutions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	37	and	CC	O	O	O
9	38	seemed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	39	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
9	40	be	VB	O	I-VP	O
9	41	indirectly	RB	O	I-VP	O
9	42	criticizing	VBG	O	I-VP	O
9	43	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	44	United	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
9	45	States	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-LocCoun
9	46	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	47	usurping	VBG	O	B-VP	O
9	48	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	49	power	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	50	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	51	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	52	United	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
9	53	Nations	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-Loc
9	54	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	``	``	O	O	O
10	1	What	WP	O	B-NP	O
10	2	I	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	3	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
10	4	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	5	mind	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	6	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
10	7	attempts	NNS	O	B-NP	O
10	8	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
10	9	undercut	VB	O	I-VP	O
10	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	11	Charter-stipulated	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
10	12	powers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
10	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	15	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
10	16	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
10	17	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
10	18	use	VB	O	I-VP	O
10	19	coercive	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	20	measuresCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	21	''	''	O	O	O
10	22	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	23	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	24	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	``	``	O	O	O
11	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
11	2	must	MD	O	B-VP	O
11	3	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
11	4	allow	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	5	creation	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	7	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	8	precedent	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	9	involving	VBG	O	B-VP	O
11	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	11	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	13	military	JJ	O	B-NP	O
11	14	power	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	15	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	16	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	17	crisis	NN	O	I-NP	B-Medical
11	18	without	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	20	support	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	21	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	22	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	23	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
11	24	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	25	.	.	O	O	O
11	26	''	''	O	O	O

12	0	Narrowing	VBG	O	O	O
12	1	in	IN	O	O	O
12	2	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	3	Kosovo	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
12	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	5	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
12	6	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	7	that	IN	O	O	O
12	8	``	``	O	O	O
12	9	political	JJ	O	B-NP	O
12	10	logic	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	11	must	MD	O	B-VP	O
12	12	prevail	VB	O	I-VP	O
12	13	''	''	O	O	O
12	14	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	15	solving	VBG	O	B-VP	O
12	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	17	civil	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	18	conflict	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	19	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	American	JJ	O	B-NP	B-LangRace
13	1	officials	NNS	O	I-NP	O
13	2	agree	VBP	O	B-VP	O
13	3	that	IN	O	O	O
13	4	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
13	5	would	MD	O	B-VP	O
13	6	prefer	VB	O	I-VP	O
13	7	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	8	political	JJ	O	I-NP	O
13	9	solution	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	11	but	CC	O	O	O
13	12	take	VB	O	B-VP	O
13	13	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	14	position	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	15	that	IN	O	O	O
13	16	Washington	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
13	17	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
13	18	NATO	NNP	O	I-NP	O
13	19	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
13	20	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	21	authority	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	22	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
13	23	use	VB	O	I-VP	O
13	24	force	NN	O	B-NP	O
13	25	without	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	26	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	27	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
13	28	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
13	29	resolution	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	30	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	``	``	O	O	O
14	1	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	2	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	3	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	4	power	NN	O	B-NP	O
14	5	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
14	6	resolve	VB	O	I-VP	O
14	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	8	Kosovo	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	9	conflict	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	10	might	MD	O	B-VP	O
14	11	lead	VB	O	I-VP	O
14	12	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
14	13	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	14	big	JJ	O	I-NP	O
14	15	war	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	16	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	17	unpredictable	JJ	O	B-NP	O
14	18	consequences	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	19	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	20	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	21	Balkan	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	22	region	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	23	and	CC	O	O	O
14	24	Europe	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
14	25	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	26	largeCOMMA	NN	O	B-NP	O
14	27	''	''	O	O	O
14	28	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
14	29	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
14	30	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	Turning	VBG	O	O	O
16	1	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
16	2	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
16	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	4	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	5	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
16	6	that	IN	O	O	O
16	7	Russia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
16	8	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
16	9	concerned	JJ	O	O	O
16	10	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	11	rising	VBG	O	B-NP	O
16	12	tensions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	13	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	15	region	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	17	where	WRB	O	O	O
16	18	Iran	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
16	19	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
16	20	Afghanistan	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
16	21	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
16	22	now	RB	O	I-VP	O
16	23	armed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
16	24	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	25	each	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	26	other	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	27	over	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	28	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	29	common	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	30	border	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	31	.	.	O	O	O

17	0	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	1	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	2	context	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
17	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	5	Russian	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
17	6	foreign	JJ	O	I-NP	O
17	7	minister	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
17	8	called	VBD	O	B-VP	O
17	9	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	10	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	11	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
17	12	look	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	13	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	15	embargo	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	16	that	WDT	O	B-NP	O
17	17	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
17	18	crippled	VBN	O	I-VP	O
17	19	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
17	20	since	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	21	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
17	22	invasion	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	24	Kuwait	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
17	25	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	26	1990	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
17	27	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	``	``	O	O	O
18	1	No	DT	O	O	O
18	2	doubt	VBP	O	B-VP	O
18	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
18	4	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
18	5	must	MD	O	B-VP	O
18	6	fully	RB	O	I-VP	O
18	7	travel	VB	O	I-VP	O
18	8	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
18	9	part	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	12	road	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
18	14	resume	VBP	O	B-VP	O
18	15	full	JJ	O	B-NP	O
18	16	cooperation	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	17	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	19	United	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgPolBody
18	20	Nations	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
18	21	Special	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
18	22	Commission	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
18	23	and	CC	O	O	I-OrgPolBody
18	24	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-OrgPolBody
18	25	IAEA	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
18	26	and	CC	O	O	O
18	27	implement	VBP	O	B-VP	O
18	28	relevant	JJ	O	B-NP	O
18	29	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
18	30	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
18	31	resolutionsCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	32	''	''	O	O	O
18	33	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
18	34	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	35	.	.	O	O	O

19	0	``	``	O	O	O
19	1	On	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	3	other	JJ	O	I-NP	O
19	4	hand	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
19	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	7	Security	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
19	8	Council	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
19	9	must	MD	O	B-VP	O
19	10	adequately	RB	O	I-VP	O
19	11	assess	VB	O	I-VP	O
19	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	13	situation	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	14	related	VBD	O	B-VP	O
19	15	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
19	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	17	elimination	NN	O	I-NP	B-Medical
19	18	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	19	Iraq	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
19	20	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
19	21	weapons	NNS	O	I-NP	O
19	22	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	23	mass	NN	O	B-NP	O
19	24	destruction	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	25	and	CC	O	O	O
19	26	answer	VB	O	B-VP	O
19	27	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	28	question	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	29	whether	IN	O	O	O
19	30	or	CC	O	O	O
19	31	not	RB	O	O	O
19	32	that	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	33	country	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	34	still	RB	O	O	O
19	35	poses	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
19	36	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	37	threat	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	38	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
19	39	regional	JJ	O	B-NP	O
19	40	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
19	41	international	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Jour
19	42	security	NN	O	I-NP	I-Jour
19	43	after	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	44	seven	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
19	45	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
19	46	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	47	work	NN	O	B-NP	O
19	48	carried	VBN	O	B-VP	O
19	49	out	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	50	there	RB	O	O	O
19	51	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	52	U.N.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
19	53	inspectors	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
19	54	.	.	O	O	O
19	55	''	''	O	O	O

20	0	Ivanov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
20	1	also	RB	O	O	O
20	2	made	VBD	O	B-VP	O
20	3	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	4	strong	JJ	O	I-NP	O
20	5	plea	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	6	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
20	7	India	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
20	8	and	CC	O	O	O
20	9	Pakistan	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
20	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
20	11	without	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	12	naming	VBG	O	B-VP	O
20	13	them	PRP	O	B-NP	O
20	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
20	15	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
20	16	adhere	VB	O	I-VP	O
20	17	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
20	18	treaties	NNS	O	B-NP	O
20	19	banning	VBG	O	B-VP	O
20	20	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	21	testing	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	22	and	CC	O	O	O
20	23	spread	VBP	O	B-VP	O
20	24	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	25	nuclear	JJ	O	B-NP	O
20	26	weapons	NNS	O	I-NP	O
20	27	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
20	28	arms	NNS	O	I-NP	O
20	29	technology	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	30	.	.	O	O	O

21	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
21	1	repeated	VBD	O	B-VP	O
21	2	Primakov	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
21	3	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
21	4	pledge	NN	O	I-NP	O
21	5	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
21	6	press	VB	O	I-VP	O
21	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	8	lower	JJR	O	I-NP	O
21	9	house	NN	O	I-NP	O
21	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	12	Russian	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
21	13	Parliament	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
21	14	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	15	ratification	NN	O	B-NP	O
21	16	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	18	Start	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
21	19	II	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
21	20	arms	NNS	O	I-NP	O
21	21	treaty	NN	O	I-NP	O
21	22	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	24	United	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
21	25	States	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-LocCoun
21	26	.	.	O	O	O

22	0	Until	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	1	that	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	2	arms-reduction	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	3	pact	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	4	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
22	5	ratified	VBN	O	I-VP	O
22	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
22	7	there	EX	O	B-NP	O
22	8	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
22	9	little	JJ	O	B-NP	O
22	10	likelihood	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	11	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	12	opening	VBG	O	B-VP	O
22	13	new	JJ	O	B-NP	O
22	14	talks	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	15	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	16	further	JJ	O	B-NP	O
22	17	cuts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	18	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	20	two	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
22	21	nations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	22	'	POS	O	B-NP	O
22	23	arsenals	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	24	.	.	O	O	O
