0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	14	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	52	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	Entertainment	NN	O	O	O
1	1	and	CC	O	O	O
1	2	culture	NN	O	O	O
1	3	stories	NNS	O	O	O
1	4	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	5	sight	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	6	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	7	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	8	hour	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	10	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	11	N.Y.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	12	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	13	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	14	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	15	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	16	Tuesday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	17	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	18	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	19	22	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
1	20	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	1	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
2	2	and	CC	O	O	O
2	3	repeats	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
2	4	call	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	6	News	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	7	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	8	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	9	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	10	888	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	11	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	12	346-9867	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	13	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	And	CC	O	O	O
3	1	be	VB	O	B-VP	O
3	2	sure	JJ	O	O	O
3	3	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	4	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	5	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	6	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	7	entertainment	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	8	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	10	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	11	partners	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	12	:	:	O	O	O
3	13	Bloomberg	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	14	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	20	Cox	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	21	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	22	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	24	Hearst	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	25	Newspapers	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	26	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	27	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	28	Houston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	29	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	30	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	31	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	32	Arizona	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
3	33	Republic	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocStat
3	34	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	35	Kansas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	36	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	37	Star	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	38	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	39	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	40	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	41	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	42	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	43	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	44	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	45	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	46	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	47	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	48	San	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
3	49	Francisco	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	50	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	51	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
3	52	Seattle	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
3	53	Post-Intelligencer	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	54	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	FRANCE-PEONY	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	2	Paris	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
4	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	4	_	NN	O	O	O
4	5	France	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
4	6	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	7	canceled	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	8	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	9	production	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	12	Chinese	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
4	13	Opera	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	14	``	``	O	I-NP	O
4	15	Peony	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Plant
4	16	Pavilion	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	17	.	.	O	O	O
4	18	''	''	O	O	O

5	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	1	Alan	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	2	Riding	VBG	O	O	I-Peop
5	3	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	THEROUX-BOOK-REVIEW	NNP	O	O	O
6	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
6	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
6	4	_	NN	O	O	O
6	5	``	``	O	O	O
6	6	Sir	NNP	O	B-NP	O
6	7	Vidia	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
6	8	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
6	9	Shadow	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	10	:	:	O	O	O
6	11	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	12	Friendship	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	13	Across	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	14	Five	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
6	15	ContinentsCOMMA	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	16	''	''	O	O	O
6	17	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	18	Paul	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	19	Theroux	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	20	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	21	Houghton	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
6	22	Mifflin	NNP	O	O	I-Loc
6	23	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
6	24	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Reviewed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
7	1	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	2	Michiko	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	3	Kakutani	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	4	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	TV-REVIEW	NNP	O	O	B-OrgCorp
8	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
8	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
8	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
8	4	_	NN	O	B-NP	O
8	5	``	``	O	O	O
8	6	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	7	Hughleys	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	8	''	''	O	O	O
8	9	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
8	10	ABC	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
8	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	12	8	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
8	13	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
8	14	30	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
8	15	p.m.	NN	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
8	16	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
8	17	and	CC	O	O	O
8	18	``	``	O	O	O
8	19	Encore	NNP	O	O	O
8	20	!	NN	O	O	O

9	0	Encore	NNP	O	O	O
9	1	!	NN	O	O	O
9	2	''	''	O	O	O

10	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
10	1	NBC	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
10	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	3	8	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
10	4	:	:	O	O	I-Num
10	5	30	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
10	6	P.M	NNP	O	I-NP	O
10	7	.	.	O	O	O
10	8	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
10	9	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	Reviewed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
11	1	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	2	Caryn	NNP	O	B-NP	O
11	3	James	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	4	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	CULTURE-NOTES	NNP	O	O	O
12	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
12	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
12	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
12	4	_	NN	O	B-NP	O
12	5	Short	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Peop
12	6	items	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	7	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	9	world	NN	O	I-NP	B-Jour
12	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	I-Jour
12	11	music	NN	O	B-NP	I-Jour
12	12	and	CC	O	O	O
12	13	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	14	arts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	15	.	.	O	O	O
