0	0	1999-09-23	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	19	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	55	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	2	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	3	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
1	4	now	RB	O	I-VP	O
1	5	scheduled	VBN	O	I-VP	O
1	6	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	8	Fort	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	9	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	10	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	11	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	12	clients	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	15	NYTimes	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	16	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	17	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	18	:	:	O	O	O
1	19	&	CC	O	O	O
1	20	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	21	;	:	O	O	O
1	22	&	CC	O	O	O
1	23	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	24	;	:	O	O	O

2	0	CHURCHSHOOTING-OFFICERS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
2	1	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
2	2	QL	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	3	;	:	O	O	O

3	0	FORT	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	1	WORTH	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
3	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	3	Texas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocStat
3	4	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	5	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	6	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	9	officers	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	10	first	JJ	O	O	B-Num
3	11	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	13	scene	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	14	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	15	Wedgwood	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
3	16	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	17	Church	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	18	last	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	19	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	20	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	21	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	22	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	23	almost	RB	O	O	O
3	24	more	RBR	O	O	O
3	25	than	IN	O	O	O
3	26	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	27	could	MD	O	B-VP	O
3	28	handle	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	29	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	1	first	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
4	2	body	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	4	homicide	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	5	lieutenant	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
4	6	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	7	charge	VBP	O	B-NP	O
4	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	10	case	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	11	saw	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	12	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	13	that	IN	O	O	O
4	14	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	15	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	16	personal	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	17	friend	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	18	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	1	another	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	2	officer	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
5	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	4	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	5	brought	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	6	back	VBP	O	O	O
5	7	memories	NNS	O	B-NP	O
5	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	10	night	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	11	she	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	12	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	13	shot	VBN	O	I-VP	O
5	14	three	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
5	15	times	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	16	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	1	KATHY	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	2	SANDERS	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	3	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Story	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	1	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
7	2	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
7	3	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	4	``	``	O	O	O
7	5	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	6	''	''	O	I-NP	O
7	7	general	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
7	8	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	9	category.	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	10	&	CC	O	O	O
7	11	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	12	;	:	O	O	O

8	0	&	CC	O	O	O
8	1	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	2	;	:	O	O	O

9	0	&	CC	O	O	O
9	1	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
9	2	;	:	O	O	O

10	0	DRAGGING-DEATH	NNP	O	B-NP	O
10	1	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
10	2	QL	NNP	O	I-NP	O
10	3	;	:	O	O	O

11	0	BRYAN	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
11	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	2	Texas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocStat
11	3	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	4	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	5	one-time	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	6	exalted	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	7	cyclops	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	9	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	10	prison	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	11	Klan	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	12	gang	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	13	blinked	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	14	back	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	15	tears	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
11	16	Thursday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
11	17	when	WRB	O	O	O
11	18	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	19	jury	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	20	sentenced	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	21	him	PRP	O	B-NP	O
11	22	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
11	23	death	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	24	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	25	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	26	torture-slaying	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	27	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	28	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	29	disabled	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	30	black	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Color
11	31	man	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	32	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	33	East	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
11	34	Texas	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
11	35	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	1	BARRY	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
12	2	SHLACHTER	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
12	3	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	Story	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	1	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
13	2	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
13	3	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	4	``	``	O	O	O
13	5	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	6	''	''	O	I-NP	O
13	7	general	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
13	8	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	9	category.	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	10	&	CC	O	O	O
13	11	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
13	12	;	:	O	O	O

14	0	&	CC	O	O	O
14	1	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	2	;	:	O	O	O

15	0	&	CC	O	O	O
15	1	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
15	2	;	:	O	O	O

16	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
16	1	Visit	NNP	O	B-VP	O
16	2	the	DT	O	O	O
16	3	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	O	B-Org
16	4	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
16	5	online	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	6	services	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	7	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	9	World	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	10	Wide	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
16	11	Web	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
16	12	:	:	O	O	O
16	13	www.star-telegram.com	NN	O	B-NP	O
16	14	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
16	15	&	CC	O	O	O
16	16	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	17	;	:	O	O	O
16	18	nn	NN	O	B-NP	O
