0	0	1999-09-23	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	16	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	45	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	2	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	3	plans	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	4	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
1	5	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	7	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	8	1999	CD	O	I-NP	B-Date
1	9	Ryder	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	10	Cup	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	11	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	12	tonight	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	13	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	14	immediate	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	15	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	16	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	17	NYTimes	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
1	18	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	19	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	20	clients	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	21	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	All	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	1	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	2	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
2	3	bear	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	5	BOS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	6	designator	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	7	and	CC	O	O	O
2	8	move	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	9	under	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	11	Sports	NNPS	O	I-NP	O
2	12	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	I-NP	O
2	13	s	PRP	O	I-NP	O
2	14	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
2	15	category	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	16	code	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	17	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	&	CC	O	O	O
3	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	2	;	:	O	O	O
3	3	&	CC	O	O	O
3	4	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	5	;	:	O	O	O
3	6	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	7	questions	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	9	contact	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	11	NYTimes	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	12	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	13	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	14	desk	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	15	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	20	&	CC	O	O	O
3	21	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	22	;	:	O	O	O
3	23	617-929-2597.	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	24	&	CC	O	O	O
3	25	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	26	;	:	O	O	O

4	0	&	CC	O	O	O
4	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	2	;	:	O	O	O
4	3	&	CC	O	O	O
4	4	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	5	;	:	O	O	O

5	0	&	CC	O	O	O
5	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
5	2	;	:	O	O	O
5	3	SPORTS	NNP	O	B-NP	O
5	4	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	I-NP	O
5	5	s	PRP	O	I-NP	O
5	6	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
5	7	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
5	8	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
5	9	;	:	O	O	O

6	0	GLF-RYDER-DAY-ONE	NNP	O	O	O
6	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
6	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
6	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
6	6	_	NN	O	O	O
6	7	Topped	NNP	O	B-NP	O
6	8	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	10	dream	VBP	O	I-NP	O
6	11	matchup	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	13	Tiger	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	14	Woods	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	15	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	16	Sergio	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	17	Garcia	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	18	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	19	the	DT	O	O	O
6	20	much	RB	O	O	O
6	21	anticipated	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	22	1999	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
6	23	Ryder	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	24	Cup	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	25	competition	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	26	begins	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	27	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	1	Joe	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	2	Concannon.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	3	1500	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
7	4	words	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	5	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	GLF-RYDER-MATCH1	NNP	O	O	O
8	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
8	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
8	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
8	6	_	NN	O	O	O
8	7	Duval-Mickelson	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	8	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	9	Montgomerie-Lawrie	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	10	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	1	Mark	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	2	Blaudschun	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
9	3	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	GLF-RYDER-MATCH2	NNP	O	O	O
10	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
10	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
10	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
10	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
10	6	_	NN	O	O	O
10	7	Woods-Lehman	NNP	O	B-NP	O
10	8	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	9	Garcia-Parnevik	NNP	O	B-NP	O
10	10	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	1	Jim	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
11	2	McCabe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
11	3	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	GLF-RYDER-MATCH3	NNP	O	O	O
12	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
12	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
12	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
12	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
12	6	_	NN	O	O	O
12	7	Love-Stewart	NNP	O	B-NP	O
12	8	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	9	Jiminez-Harrington	NNP	O	B-NP	O
12	10	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	1	Bob	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	2	Duffy	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	3	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	GLF-RYDER-MATCH4	NNP	O	O	O
14	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
14	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
14	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
14	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
14	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
14	6	_	NN	O	O	O
14	7	Maggert-Sutton	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	8	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	9	Clarke-Westwood	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	10	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	1	Bob	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
15	2	Duffy	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
15	3	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	GLF-RYDER-MONTGOMERIE	NNP	O	O	O
16	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
16	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
16	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
16	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
16	6	_	NN	O	O	O
16	7	Ninety-nine	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	8	percent	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	9	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	11	time	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	13	Colin	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	14	Montgomerie	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
16	15	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
16	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	17	sportsman	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	18	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
16	19	ideal	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	20	:	:	O	O	O
16	21	charming	JJ	O	O	O
16	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	23	deferential	JJ	O	O	O
16	24	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	25	gracious	JJ	O	O	O
16	26	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	27	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	28	quintessential	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	29	gentleman	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	30	.	.	O	O	O

17	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	1	Bob	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
17	2	Duffy	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
17	3	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
18	1	2	CD	O	O	B-Num
18	2	takes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
18	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

19	0	w	NN	O	O	O

20	0	GLF-RYDER-WOODS	NNP	O	O	O
20	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
20	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
20	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
20	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
20	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
20	6	_	NN	O	O	O
20	7	Tiger	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
20	8	Woods	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
20	9	now	RB	O	B-VP	O
20	10	known	VBN	O	I-VP	O
20	11	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
20	12	most	JJS	O	B-NP	O
20	13	Americans	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
20	14	_	NN	O	O	O
20	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	16	golf	NN	O	I-NP	B-Sport
20	17	magician	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	18	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	20	Nike	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
20	21	commercial	JJ	O	I-NP	O
20	22	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	23	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
20	24	leaped	VBN	O	I-VP	O
20	25	virtually	RB	O	O	O
20	26	free-form	JJ	O	O	O
20	27	and	CC	O	O	O
20	28	spontaneous	JJ	O	O	O
20	29	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	30	that	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	31	static	JJ	O	I-NP	O
20	32	world	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	33	.	.	O	O	O

21	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	1	Michael	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
21	2	Madden	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
21	3	.	.	O	O	O

22	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
22	1	2	CD	O	O	B-Num
22	2	takes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
22	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O

23	0	&	CC	O	O	O
23	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
23	2	;	:	O	O	O
23	3	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
23	4	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
23	5	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
23	6	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
23	7	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
23	8	;	:	O	O	O
23	9	&	CC	O	O	O
23	10	QC	NNP	O	B-NP	O
23	11	;	:	O	O	O
