0	0	2000-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	15	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	47	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	&	CC	O	O	O
0	5	HT	NNP	O	B-NP	O
0	6	;	:	O	O	O

1	0	WASHINGTON	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	1	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	2	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	3	road	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	4	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
1	5	nursing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
1	6	home	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	7	improvement	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	8	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	9	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
1	10	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	11	tortuous	JJ	O	I-NP	O
1	12	one	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
1	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	14	missed	VBN	O	B-NP	O
1	15	deadlines	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	16	and	CC	O	O	O
1	17	unfinished	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	18	agendas	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	19	even	RB	O	O	O
1	20	as	IN	O	O	O
1	21	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	22	pace	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	24	new	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	25	proposals	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	26	accelerates	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	27	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	_	NN	O	O	O
2	1	Enforcement	NNP	O	O	O
2	2	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	4	Nursing	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	5	Home	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	6	Reform	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	7	Act	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
2	9	1987	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
2	11	set	VBD	O	B-VP	I-Org
2	12	to	TO	O	I-VP	I-Org
2	13	begin	VB	O	I-VP	I-Org
2	14	in	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
2	15	1990	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
2	17	was	VBD	O	B-VP	I-Org
2	18	delayed	VBN	O	I-VP	I-Org
2	19	until	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
2	20	1995	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	21	because	IN	O	O	I-Org
2	22	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	23	Health	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	24	and	CC	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	25	Human	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	26	Services	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	27	Department	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	28	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	29	HHS	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgUniv
2	30	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	31	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	32	late	JJ	O	O	O
2	33	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	34	completing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
2	35	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	36	necessary	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	37	regulations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	38	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	_	NN	O	O	O
3	1	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	2	1998	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
3	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	4	congressional	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	5	investigators	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	6	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	8	U.S.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
3	9	General	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgPolBody
3	10	Accounting	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
3	11	Office	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
3	12	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	13	probing	VBG	O	I-VP	O
3	14	California	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocStat
3	15	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
3	16	nursing	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	17	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	18	and	CC	O	O	O
3	19	finding	VBG	O	B-VP	O
3	20	that	IN	O	O	O
3	21	30	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumPercent
3	22	percent	NN	O	I-NP	I-NumPercent
3	23	had	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	24	health	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	25	violations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	26	that	IN	O	B-NP	O
3	27	caused	VBN	O	B-NP	O
3	28	injury	NN	O	I-NP	B-Medical
3	29	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
3	30	death	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	31	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
3	32	residents	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	33	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	34	or	CC	O	O	O
3	35	had	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	36	falsified	VBN	O	I-VP	O
3	37	records	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	38	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	39	hide	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	40	deficiencies	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	41	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	Just	RB	O	B-NP	O
4	1	a	DT	O	I-NP	O
4	2	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	3	before	IN	O	O	O
4	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	5	scheduled	VBN	O	I-NP	O
4	6	release	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	9	report	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	11	President	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
4	12	Clinton	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
4	13	announced	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	14	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	15	crackdown	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	16	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	18	worst	JJS	O	I-NP	O
4	19	nursing	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	20	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	21	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	22	including	VBG	O	B-PP	O
4	23	surprise	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	24	weekend	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	25	inspections	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	26	and	CC	O	O	O
4	27	immediate	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	28	fines	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	29	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	30	violating	VBG	O	B-VP	O
4	31	standards	NNS	O	B-NP	O
4	32	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	_	NN	O	O	O
5	1	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	2	1999	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
5	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	4	federal	JJ	O	B-NP	O
5	5	investigators	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
5	6	continued	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	7	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
5	8	find	VB	O	I-VP	O
5	9	major	JJ	O	B-NP	O
5	10	health	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	11	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
5	12	safety	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	13	violations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	14	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	1	HHS	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgUniv
6	2	inspector	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
6	3	general	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
6	4	reported	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	5	that	IN	O	O	O
6	6	``	``	O	O	O
6	7	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	8	nursing	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	9	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	10	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
6	11	chronically	RB	O	O	O
6	12	substandard	JJ	O	O	O
6	13	''	''	O	O	O
6	14	and	CC	O	O	O
6	15	that	IN	O	O	O
6	16	complaints	NNS	O	B-NP	O
6	17	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	18	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	20	rise	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	21	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	That	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	1	year	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	3	Congress	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	4	passed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
7	5	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	6	law	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	7	forbidding	VBG	O	B-VP	O
7	8	nursing	NN	O	B-NP	O
7	9	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	10	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	11	evicting	VBG	O	B-VP	O
7	12	Medicaid	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	13	recipients	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	14	after	IN	O	O	O
7	15	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	16	facilities	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	17	began	VBD	O	B-VP	O
7	18	trying	VBG	O	I-VP	O
7	19	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
7	20	replace	VB	O	I-VP	O
7	21	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	22	residents	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	23	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	24	higher-paying	JJ	O	B-NP	O
7	25	clients	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	26	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	_	NN	O	O	O
8	1	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	2	2000	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
8	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	4	Democratic	JJ	O	B-NP	B-OrgPolBody
8	5	congressional	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	6	investigators	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
8	7	began	VBD	O	B-VP	O
8	8	checking	VBG	O	I-VP	O
8	9	conditions	NNS	O	B-NP	O
8	10	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	11	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	12	sampling	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	14	congressional	JJ	O	B-NP	O
8	15	districts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	16	and	CC	O	O	O
8	17	finding	VBG	O	B-VP	O
8	18	serious	JJ	O	B-NP	O
8	19	health	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	20	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
8	21	safety	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	22	problems	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	23	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	_	NN	O	O	O
9	1	This	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	2	summer	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	4	eight	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
9	5	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
9	6	late	RB	O	O	O
9	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	8	HHS	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgUniv
9	9	delivered	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	10	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	11	ground-breaking	JJ	O	I-NP	O
9	12	report	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	13	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	15	ill	JJ	O	I-NP	O
9	16	effects	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	17	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	18	understaffing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
9	19	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	20	more	RBR	O	B-NP	O
9	21	than	IN	O	I-NP	O
9	22	half	DT	O	I-NP	O
9	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	24	America	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
9	25	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
9	26	nursing	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	27	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	28	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	1	study	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	2	had	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	3	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	4	ordered	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	5	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	6	Congress	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgPolBody
10	7	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	8	completion	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	10	1992	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
10	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	12	but	CC	O	O	O
10	13	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	14	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	15	all	DT	O	I-VP	O
10	16	but	CC	O	I-VP	O
10	17	forgotten	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	18	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	19	lawmakers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
10	20	and	CC	O	O	O
10	21	HHS	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgUniv
10	22	until	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	23	Sen.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
10	24	Charles	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
10	25	Grassley	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
10	26	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Peop
10	27	R-Iowa	NNP	O	O	I-Peop
10	28	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	29	chairman	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	30	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	31	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	32	Senate	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgPolBody
10	33	Aging	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
10	34	Committee	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgPolBody
10	35	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	36	brought	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	37	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	38	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
10	39	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	40	attention	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	41	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	42	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	43	Clinton	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
10	44	administration	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	45	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	1	response	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	3	President	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
11	4	Clinton	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
11	5	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	6	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
11	7	16	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
11	8	proposed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	9	$1	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
11	10	billion	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
11	11	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	12	grants	NNS	O	B-NP	O
11	13	over	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	15	next	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	16	five	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
11	17	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
11	18	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
11	19	boost	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	20	staffing	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	21	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	22	some	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	23	nursing	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	24	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	25	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
12	1	also	RB	O	O	O
12	2	announced	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	3	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
12	4	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	5	ordering	VBG	O	I-VP	O
12	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	7	Health	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
12	8	Care	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
12	9	Financing	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
12	10	Administration	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
12	11	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
12	12	establish	VB	O	I-VP	O
12	13	mandatory	JJ	O	B-NP	O
12	14	minimum	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	15	standards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	16	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	17	staffing	VBG	O	B-NP	O
12	18	levels	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	19	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	20	nursing	VBG	O	B-NP	O
12	21	homes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	23	but	CC	O	O	O
12	24	not	RB	O	O	O
12	25	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	26	at	IN	O	B-NP	O
12	27	least	JJS	O	I-NP	O
12	28	two	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
12	29	more	JJR	O	I-NP	O
12	30	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
12	31	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	ENDIT	NNP	O	O	O

14	0	Story	NNP	O	O	O
14	1	Filed	NNP	O	O	O
14	2	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	3	Cox	NNP	O	O	O
14	4	Newspapers	NNP	O	O	O

