0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	16	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	04	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	Sports	NNPS	O	O	O
1	1	stories	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	2	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	3	sight	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	4	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	5	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	6	hour	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	7	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	8	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	9	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
1	10	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	11	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	12	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	13	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	14	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	15	&	CC	O	O	O
1	16	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	17	;	:	O	O	O
1	18	TUESDAY	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	19	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
1	20	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	21	;	:	O	O	O
1	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	23	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	24	22	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
1	25	:	:	O	O	O

2	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	1	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
2	2	and	CC	O	O	O
2	3	repeats	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
2	4	call	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	6	News	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	7	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	8	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	9	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	10	888	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	11	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	12	346-9867	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	13	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	And	CC	O	O	O
3	1	be	VB	O	B-VP	O
3	2	sure	JJ	O	O	O
3	3	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	4	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	5	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	6	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	7	sports	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	8	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	10	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	11	partners	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	12	:	:	O	O	O
3	13	Bloomberg	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	14	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	20	Cox	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
3	21	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	22	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
3	24	Hearst	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
3	25	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	26	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	28	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	29	Houston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	30	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	32	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	33	Arizona	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
3	34	Republic	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocStat
3	35	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	36	Kansas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	37	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	38	Star	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	39	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	40	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	41	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	42	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	43	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	44	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	45	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	46	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	47	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	48	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	49	San	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
3	50	Francisco	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	51	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	52	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
3	53	Seattle	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
3	54	Post-Intelligencer	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	55	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	RUN-OBIT-GRIFFITH-JOYNER	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
4	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	4	_	NN	O	O	O
4	5	Track	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	6	star	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	7	Florence	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
4	8	Griffith-Joyner	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
4	9	died	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	10	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	11	morning	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	12	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	13	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
4	14	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
4	15	after	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	16	suffering	VBG	O	B-VP	O
4	17	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	18	seizure	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	19	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	1	Jere	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	2	Longman	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
5	3	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	RUN-RHODEN-COLUMN	NNP	O	O	O
6	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	2	East	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
6	3	Rutherford	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
6	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	5	N.J.	NNP	O	O	B-Org
6	6	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	I-Org
6	7	_	NN	O	O	I-Org
6	8	Sports	NNPS	O	B-NP	I-Org
6	9	of	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
6	10	The	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
6	11	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
6	12	column	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	13	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	14	FloJo	NNP	O	B-NP	O
6	15	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
6	16	sudden	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	17	death	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	18	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	19	her	PP$	O	B-NP	O
6	20	great	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	21	accomplishments	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	22	and	CC	O	O	O
6	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	24	way	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	25	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	26	suspicions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	27	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	28	drug	NN	O	B-NP	B-Medical
6	29	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	30	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
6	31	linger	VB	O	I-VP	O
6	32	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	33	her	PP$	O	B-NP	O
6	34	legacy	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	35	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	1	William	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	2	C.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	3	Rhode	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	4	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	FBN-GIANTS-COWBOYS	NNP	O	O	O
8	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
8	2	East	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	3	Rutherford	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
8	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
8	5	N.J.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
8	6	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
8	7	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	8	Giants	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
8	9	vs.	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	10	Cowboys	NNPS	O	B-NP	B-OrgTeam
8	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	12	8	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
8	13	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
8	14	20	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
8	15	p.m	RB	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
8	16	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	ET	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Perform
9	1	start	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	2	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	1	Bill	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
10	2	Pennington	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
10	3	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	Other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
11	1	football	NN	O	I-NP	B-Sport
11	2	as	IN	O	O	O
11	3	needed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
11	4	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	BBA-YANKS-INDIANS	NNP	O	O	O
12	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
12	2	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
12	3	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
12	4	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
12	5	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	6	Cleveland	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
12	7	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	9	Yankees	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
12	10	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	1	Selena	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	2	Roberts	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	3	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	BBA-RIPKEN	NNP	O	O	O
14	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
14	2	Baltimore	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
14	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
14	4	_	NN	O	O	O
14	5	How	WRB	O	O	O
14	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	7	Cal	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
14	8	Ripken	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
14	9	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
14	10	big	JJ	O	I-NP	O
14	11	streak	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	12	came	VBD	O	B-VP	O
14	13	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
14	14	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	15	end	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	16	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	1	Buster	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
15	2	Olney	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
15	3	.	.	O	O	O
