0	0	1999-09-22	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	19	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	30	CD	O	O	I-Num
0	4	TEXAS	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
0	5	PASTORS	NNP	O	O	B-ProfTitle
0	6	HAIL	NNP	O	O	O
0	7	NEW	NNP	O	O	O
0	8	NATIONAL	NNP	O	O	O
0	9	BAPTIST	NNP	O	O	O
0	10	LEADER	NN	O	O	B-ProfTitle

1	0	FORT	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	1	WORTH	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
1	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	3	Texas	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
1	4	_	NN	O	O	O
1	5	Local	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	6	church	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	7	officials	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	8	say	VBP	O	B-VP	O
1	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	10	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
1	11	president	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
1	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	13	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	14	National	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	15	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	16	Convention	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	17	USA	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	18	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	20	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
1	21	William	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	22	J.	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	23	Shaw	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	24	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	25	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
1	26	help	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	27	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	28	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	29	rise	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	30	above	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	31	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	32	damaging	JJ	O	I-NP	O
1	33	scandal	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	34	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	``	``	O	O	O
2	1	Dr.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	2	Shaw	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
2	3	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
2	4	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
2	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	7	finest	JJS	O	I-NP	O
2	8	men	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	11	country	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	13	and	CC	O	O	O
2	14	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
2	15	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
2	16	make	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	18	changes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	19	needed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	20	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
2	21	bring	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	22	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
2	23	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	24	into	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	25	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	26	21st	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
2	27	centuryCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	28	''	''	O	O	O
2	29	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	30	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	31	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	32	Cedric	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	33	Britt	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	34	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	35	pastor	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	36	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	37	Mount	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
2	38	Gilead	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	39	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	40	Church	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	41	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	42	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
2	43	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
2	44	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	2	65	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	4	pastor	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	6	White	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
3	7	Rock	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	8	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	9	Church	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	10	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	11	Philadelphia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	13	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	14	elected	VBN	O	I-VP	O
3	15	last	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	16	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	17	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	18	succeed	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	20	disgraced	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	21	former	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	22	president	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	24	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	25	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	26	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	27	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	28	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	29	Henry	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	30	J.	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	31	Lyons	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	32	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	Born	VBN	O	B-VP	O
4	1	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	2	Marshall	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
4	3	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	4	East	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
4	5	Texas	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
4	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	7	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	8	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	9	dedicated	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	10	himself	PRP	O	B-NP	O
4	11	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
4	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	13	ministry	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	14	since	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	15	childhood	NN	O	B-NP	O
4	16	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	1	preached	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	2	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	3	first	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
5	4	sermon	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	5	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	6	11	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
5	7	and	CC	O	O	O
5	8	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	9	ordained	VBN	O	I-VP	O
5	10	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	11	pastor	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
5	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	13	Oak	NNP	O	B-NP	O
5	14	Hill	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
5	15	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	16	Church	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	17	near	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	18	Marshall	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
5	19	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	20	17	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
5	21	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	22	according	VBG	O	B-PP	O
5	23	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
5	24	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	25	biography	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	26	supplied	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	27	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	28	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	29	Philadelphia	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
5	30	church	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	31	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	1	graduated	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	2	summa	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	3	cum	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	4	laude	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	5	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	6	19	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
6	7	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	9	old	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	10	Bishop	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgUniv
6	11	College	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgUniv
6	12	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	13	Dallas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
6	14	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	15	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	16	major	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	17	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	18	philosophy	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	19	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
6	20	religion	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	21	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	1	also	RB	O	O	O
7	2	holds	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	3	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	4	master	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	6	divinity	NN	O	B-NP	O
7	7	degree	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	8	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	9	Union	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
7	10	Theological	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	11	Seminary	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	12	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	13	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
7	14	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
7	15	and	CC	O	O	O
7	16	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	17	doctor	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
7	18	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	19	ministry	NN	O	B-NP	O
7	20	degree	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	21	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	22	Colgate	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
7	23	Rochester	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	24	Divinity	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	25	School	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	26	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	27	Crozer	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	28	Theological	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	29	Seminary	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	30	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	31	Rochester	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
7	32	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	33	N.Y	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
7	34	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	Britt	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
8	2	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	3	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
8	4	help	VB	O	I-VP	O
8	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	6	National	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
8	7	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	8	Convention	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	9	recover	VB	O	B-VP	O
8	10	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	12	damage	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	13	caused	VBN	O	B-VP	O
8	14	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	15	Lyons	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
8	16	'	POS	O	B-NP	O
8	17	actions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	18	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	Lyons	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
9	1	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
9	2	serving	VBG	O	I-VP	O
9	3	51/2	NN	O	B-NP	B-Num
9	4	years	NNS	O	I-NP	I-Num
9	5	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	6	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	7	Florida	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
9	8	state	NN	O	I-NP	I-LocStat
9	9	prison	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	10	after	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	11	being	VBG	O	B-VP	O
9	12	convicted	VBN	O	I-VP	O
9	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	14	racketeering	NN	O	B-NP	O
9	15	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
9	16	grand	JJ	O	I-NP	O
9	17	theft	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	18	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	1	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	2	found	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	3	guilty	JJ	O	O	O
10	4	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	5	stealing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
10	6	more	JJR	O	B-NP	O
10	7	than	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	8	$4	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
10	9	million	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
10	10	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	11	corporations	NNS	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
10	12	wanting	VBG	O	B-VP	O
10	13	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
10	14	do	VB	O	I-VP	O
10	15	business	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	16	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	18	3	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
10	19	million-member	JJ	O	I-NP	O
10	20	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	21	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	22	predominantly	RB	O	B-NP	O
10	23	African-American	JJ	O	I-NP	O
10	24	churches	NNS	O	I-NP	O
10	25	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	Lyons	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
11	1	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	2	also	RB	O	I-VP	O
11	3	found	VBN	O	I-VP	O
11	4	guilty	JJ	O	O	O
11	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	6	taking	VBG	O	B-VP	O
11	7	nearly	RB	O	B-NP	O
11	8	$250COMMA000	NN	O	I-NP	B-Money
11	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	10	Anti-Defamation	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
11	11	League	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	12	funds	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	13	intended	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	14	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
11	15	help	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	16	rebuild	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	17	black	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Color
11	18	churches	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	19	burned	VBD	O	B-VP	O
11	20	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	21	arsonists	NNS	O	B-NP	O
11	22	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	Also	RB	O	O	O
12	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	2	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
12	3	admitted	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	4	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
12	5	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	6	improper	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	7	relationship	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	8	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	9	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
12	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	11	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
12	12	female	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	13	aides	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	14	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	Most	JJS	O	B-NP	O
13	1	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	3	presidential	JJ	O	I-NP	O
13	4	candidates	NNS	O	I-NP	O
13	5	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	6	last	JJ	O	B-NP	O
13	7	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	8	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
13	9	gathering	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	10	vowed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
13	11	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
13	12	make	VB	O	I-VP	O
13	13	major	JJ	O	B-NP	O
13	14	changes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
13	15	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	17	way	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	19	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	20	handles	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
13	21	money	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
13	22	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	1	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
14	2	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	3	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
14	4	first	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
14	5	acts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
14	7	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
14	8	promised	VBD	O	B-VP	O
14	9	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	10	immediate	JJ	O	I-NP	O
14	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
14	12	independent	JJ	O	I-NP	O
14	13	audit	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	14	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	16	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	17	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
14	18	finances	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	19	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	Britt	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
15	1	attended	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	3	national	JJ	O	I-NP	O
15	4	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	5	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	6	Tampa	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
15	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	8	Fla.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
15	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	10	and	CC	O	O	O
15	11	supported	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	12	another	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	13	candidate	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	16	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
15	17	E.V.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	18	Hill	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	19	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	20	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
15	21	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
15	22	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	``	``	O	O	O
16	1	I	PRP	O	B-NP	O
16	2	'm	VBP	O	B-VP	O
16	3	very	RB	O	O	O
16	4	happy	JJ	O	O	O
16	5	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	7	outcome	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	10	election	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	12	thoughCOMMA	NN	O	O	O
16	13	''	''	O	O	O
16	14	Britt	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	15	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
16	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	17	because	IN	O	O	O
16	18	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	19	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
16	20	committed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
16	21	himself	PRP	O	B-NP	O
16	22	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
16	23	restructuring	VBG	O	B-VP	O
16	24	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	25	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	26	.	.	O	O	O

17	0	``	``	O	O	O
17	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
17	2	need	VBP	O	B-VP	O
17	3	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
17	4	make	VB	O	I-VP	O
17	5	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
17	6	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	7	more	RBR	O	O	O
17	8	user-friendly	JJ	O	O	O
17	9	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
17	10	local	JJ	O	B-NP	O
17	11	churchesCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	12	''	''	O	I-NP	O
17	13	Britt	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
17	14	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
17	15	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
18	1	favors	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
18	2	giving	VBG	O	I-VP	O
18	3	loan	NN	O	B-NP	O
18	4	assistance	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	5	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
18	6	help	VB	O	I-VP	O
18	7	start	VB	O	I-VP	O
18	8	churches	NNS	O	B-NP	O
18	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	10	developing	VBG	O	B-NP	O
18	11	communities	NNS	O	I-NP	O
18	12	.	.	O	O	O

19	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	1	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
19	2	B.R.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
19	3	Daniels	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
19	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
19	5	pastor	NN	O	B-NP	I-Org
19	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
19	7	Beth-Eden	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
19	8	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
19	9	Church	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
19	10	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
19	11	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
19	12	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
19	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
19	14	also	RB	O	O	O
19	15	attended	VBD	O	B-VP	O
19	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	17	national	JJ	O	I-NP	O
19	18	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	19	and	CC	O	O	O
19	20	strongly	RB	O	B-VP	O
19	21	supported	VBD	O	I-VP	O
19	22	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
19	23	.	.	O	O	O

20	0	``	``	O	O	O
20	1	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	2	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	3	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
20	4	back	RB	O	O	O
20	5	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	7	way	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	8	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
20	9	ought	MD	O	B-VP	O
20	10	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
20	11	be	VB	O	I-VP	O
20	12	under	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	13	Bill	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
20	14	ShawCOMMA	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
20	15	''	''	O	I-NP	O
20	16	Daniels	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
20	17	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
20	18	.	.	O	O	O

21	0	``	``	O	O	O
21	1	I	PRP	O	B-NP	O
21	2	'm	VBP	O	B-VP	O
21	3	very	RB	O	O	O
21	4	grateful	JJ	O	O	O
21	5	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
21	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	7	Lord	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
21	8	.	.	O	O	O
21	9	''	''	O	O	O

22	0	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
22	1	won	VBD	O	B-VP	O
22	2	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	3	about	IN	O	B-NP	O
22	4	200	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
22	5	votes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	6	over	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	8	Rev.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
22	9	W.	NNP	O	I-NP	O
22	10	Franklyn	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
22	11	Richardson	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
22	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	13	Mount	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
22	14	Vernon	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
22	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
22	16	N.Y.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
22	17	Hill	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
22	18	came	VBD	O	B-VP	O
22	19	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	20	third	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Num
22	21	.	.	O	O	O

23	0	Daniels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
23	1	believes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
23	2	that	IN	O	O	O
23	3	Richardson	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
23	4	hurt	VBD	O	B-VP	O
23	5	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
23	6	candidacy	NN	O	I-NP	O
23	7	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
23	8	speaking	VBG	O	B-VP	O
23	9	out	IN	O	O	O
23	10	too	RB	O	O	O
23	11	harshly	RB	O	O	O
23	12	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
23	13	Lyons	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
23	14	.	.	O	O	O

24	0	``	``	O	O	O
24	1	When	WRB	O	O	O
24	2	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
24	3	man	NN	O	I-NP	O
24	4	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
24	5	already	RB	O	O	O
24	6	down	RB	O	O	O
24	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
24	8	you	PRP	O	B-NP	O
24	9	don	VB	O	B-VP	O
24	10	't	NN	O	B-NP	O
24	11	need	VB	O	B-VP	O
24	12	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
24	13	kick	VB	O	I-VP	O
24	14	himCOMMA	NN	O	B-NP	O
24	15	''	''	O	I-NP	O
24	16	Daniels	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
24	17	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
24	18	.	.	O	O	O

25	0	During	IN	O	B-PP	O
25	1	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
25	2	meeting	NN	O	I-NP	O
25	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
25	4	delegates	NNS	O	B-NP	O
25	5	took	VBD	O	B-VP	O
25	6	up	IN	O	O	O
25	7	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
25	8	offering	NN	O	I-NP	O
25	9	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
25	10	help	VB	O	I-VP	O
25	11	pay	VB	O	I-VP	O
25	12	Lyons	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
25	13	'	POS	O	B-NP	O
25	14	legal	JJ	O	I-NP	O
25	15	expenses	NNS	O	I-NP	O
25	16	.	.	O	O	O

26	0	Shaw	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
26	1	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
26	2	called	VBN	O	I-VP	O
26	3	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
26	4	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
26	5	national	JJ	O	I-NP	O
26	6	summit	NN	O	I-NP	O
26	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
26	8	pastors	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
26	9	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
26	10	discuss	VB	O	I-VP	O
26	11	changes	NNS	O	B-NP	O
26	12	needed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
26	13	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
26	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
26	15	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
26	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
26	17	Daniels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
26	18	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
26	19	.	.	O	O	O

27	0	``	``	O	O	O
27	1	Under	IN	O	B-PP	O
27	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
27	3	old	JJ	O	I-NP	O
27	4	system	NN	O	I-NP	O
27	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
27	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
27	7	board	NN	O	I-NP	O
27	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
27	9	directors	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
27	10	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
27	11	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
27	12	rubber	NN	O	I-NP	O
27	13	stamp	NN	O	I-NP	O
27	14	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
27	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
27	16	presidentCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
27	17	''	''	O	O	O
27	18	Daniels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
27	19	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
27	20	.	.	O	O	O

28	0	``	``	O	O	O
28	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
28	2	need	VBP	O	B-VP	O
28	3	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
28	4	put	VB	O	I-VP	O
28	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
28	6	convention	NN	O	I-NP	O
28	7	back	NN	O	I-NP	O
28	8	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
28	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
28	10	hands	NNS	O	I-NP	O
28	11	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
28	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
28	13	people	NNS	O	I-NP	O
28	14	.	.	O	O	O
28	15	''	''	O	O	O

29	0	Many	JJ	O	B-NP	O
29	1	churches	NNS	O	I-NP	O
29	2	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
29	3	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
29	4	giving	VBG	O	I-VP	O
29	5	token	JJ	O	B-NP	O
29	6	amounts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
29	7	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
29	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
29	9	national	JJ	O	I-NP	O
29	10	denomination	NN	O	I-NP	O
29	11	because	IN	O	O	O
29	12	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
29	13	felt	VBD	O	B-VP	O
29	14	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
29	15	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
29	16	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
29	17	getting	VBG	O	I-VP	O
29	18	enough	RB	O	O	O
29	19	out	IN	O	B-PP	O
29	20	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
29	21	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
29	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
29	23	Daniels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
29	24	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
29	25	.	.	O	O	O

30	0	Some	DT	O	B-NP	O
30	1	National	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
30	2	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
30	3	churches	NNS	O	I-NP	O
30	4	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
30	5	becoming	VBG	O	I-VP	O
30	6	aligned	VBN	O	O	O
30	7	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
30	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
30	9	Southern	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
30	10	Baptist	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Religion
30	11	Convention	NNP	O	I-NP	O
30	12	because	IN	O	B-PP	O
30	13	of	IN	O	I-PP	O
30	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
30	15	assistance	NN	O	I-NP	O
30	16	that	IN	O	O	O
30	17	denomination	NN	O	B-NP	O
30	18	gives	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
30	19	pastors	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
30	20	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
30	21	churches	NNS	O	I-NP	O
30	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
30	23	Daniels	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
30	24	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
30	25	.	.	O	O	O

31	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
31	1	Visit	NNP	O	B-VP	O
31	2	the	DT	O	O	O
31	3	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	O	B-Org
31	4	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
31	5	online	JJ	O	I-NP	O
31	6	services	NNS	O	I-NP	O
31	7	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
31	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
31	9	World	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
31	10	Wide	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
31	11	Web	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
31	12	:	:	O	O	O
31	13	www.star-telegram.com	NN	O	B-NP	O
31	14	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
31	15	&	CC	O	O	O
31	16	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
31	17	;	:	O	O	O
31	18	nn	NN	O	B-NP	O
