0	0	1998-09-23	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	15	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	27	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	Sports	NNPS	O	O	O
1	1	stories	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	2	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	3	sight	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	4	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	5	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	6	hour	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	7	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	8	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	9	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
1	10	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	11	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	12	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	13	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	14	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	15	&	CC	O	O	O
1	16	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	17	;	:	O	O	O
1	18	THURSDAY	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	19	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
1	20	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	21	;	:	O	O	O
1	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	23	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	24	24	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
1	25	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	BBN-ARATON-COLUMN	NNP	O	O	O
2	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
2	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	4	_	NN	O	O	O
2	5	Sports	NNPS	O	B-NP	O
2	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	7	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	8	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	9	column	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	10	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	12	Mets	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
2	13	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	1	Harvey	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	2	Araton	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	3	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	BBN-ANDERSON	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	2	Milwaukee	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
4	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
4	4	_	NN	O	O	O
4	5	Sports	NNPS	O	B-NP	O
4	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	7	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	8	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	9	column	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	10	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	11	Sosa	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	12	and	CC	O	O	O
4	13	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	14	Cubs	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
4	15	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	1	Dave	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	2	Anderson	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
5	3	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	BBN-METS-EXPOS	NNP	O	O	O
6	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	2	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
6	3	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
6	4	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
6	5	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	6	Montreal	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
6	7	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	8	Mets	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgTeam
6	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	10	7	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
6	11	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
6	12	40	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
6	13	p.m	RB	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
6	14	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	ET	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Perform
7	1	start	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	2	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	1	Jason	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	2	Diamos	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	3	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	BBA-YANKS-INDIANS	NNP	O	O	O
9	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
9	2	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
9	3	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
9	4	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
9	5	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	6	Cleveland	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
9	7	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	9	Yankees	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
9	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	11	7	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
9	12	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
9	13	35	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
9	14	p.m	RB	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
9	15	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	ET	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Perform
10	1	start	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	2	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	1	Buster	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
11	2	Olney	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
11	3	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	BBN-MCGWIRE	NNP	O	O	O
12	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
12	2	St	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
12	3	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	Louis	NNP	O	O	B-Peop
13	1	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
13	2	_	NN	O	O	O
13	3	Randy	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	4	Johnson	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	7	flamethrower	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	9	goes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
13	10	against	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	11	Mark	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	12	McGwire	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	15	slugger	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	16	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	1	Selena	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
14	2	Roberts	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
14	3	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	1	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
15	2	and	CC	O	O	O
15	3	repeats	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
15	4	call	VBP	O	B-VP	O
15	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	6	News	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
15	7	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
15	8	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	9	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
15	10	888	CD	O	O	B-Num
15	11	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
15	12	346-9867	CD	O	O	B-Num
15	13	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	And	CC	O	O	O
16	1	be	VB	O	B-VP	O
16	2	sure	JJ	O	O	O
16	3	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
16	4	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	5	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	6	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
16	7	sports	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	8	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	10	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
16	11	partners	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	12	:	:	O	O	O
16	13	Bloomberg	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	14	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
16	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	20	Cox	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
16	21	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	22	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
16	24	Hearst	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
16	25	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	26	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	28	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	29	Houston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
16	30	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	32	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	33	Arizona	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
16	34	Republic	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocStat
16	35	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	36	Kansas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
16	37	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
16	38	Star	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	39	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	40	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
16	41	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
16	42	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
16	43	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	44	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
16	45	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
16	46	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	47	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	48	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	49	San	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
16	50	Francisco	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	51	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
16	52	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
16	53	Seattle	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
16	54	Post-Intelligencer	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
16	55	.	.	O	O	O
