0	0	1999-09-22	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	20	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	15	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	2	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	3	plans	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	4	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
1	5	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	7	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	8	1999	CD	O	I-NP	B-Date
1	9	Ryder	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	10	Cup	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	11	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	12	tonight	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	13	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	14	immediate	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	15	use	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	16	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	17	NYTimes	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
1	18	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	19	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	20	clients	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	21	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	All	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	1	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	2	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
2	3	bear	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	5	BOS	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	6	designator	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	7	and	CC	O	O	O
2	8	move	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	9	under	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	11	Sports	NNPS	O	I-NP	O
2	12	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	I-NP	O
2	13	s	PRP	O	I-NP	O
2	14	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
2	15	category	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	16	code	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	17	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	&	CC	O	O	O
3	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	2	;	:	O	O	O
3	3	&	CC	O	O	O
3	4	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	5	;	:	O	O	O
3	6	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	7	questions	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	8	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	9	contact	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	11	NYTimes	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	12	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	13	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	14	desk	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	15	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
3	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	20	&	CC	O	O	O
3	21	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	22	;	:	O	O	O
3	23	617-929-2597.	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	24	&	CC	O	O	O
3	25	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	26	;	:	O	O	O

4	0	&	CC	O	O	O
4	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	2	;	:	O	O	O
4	3	&	CC	O	O	O
4	4	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
4	5	;	:	O	O	O

5	0	GLF-RYDER-TIGER	NNP	O	O	O
5	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
5	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
5	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
5	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
5	6	_	NN	O	O	O
5	7	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	8	never	RB	O	O	O
5	9	knew	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	10	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	11	name	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	12	had	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	13	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	14	H	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	15	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	16	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	17	until	IN	O	O	O
5	18	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	19	got	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	20	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
5	21	Clyde	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	22	Street	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
5	23	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	``	``	O	O	O
6	1	Ty-gahCOMMA	NNP	O	O	O
6	2	''	''	O	B-NP	O
6	3	people	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	4	kept	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	5	shouting	VBG	O	I-VP	O
6	6	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	7	Tiger	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	8	Woods	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
6	9	as	IN	O	O	O
6	10	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
6	11	strode	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	12	along	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	13	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	14	Country	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
6	15	Club	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgTeam
6	16	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
6	17	sodden	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	18	fairways	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	19	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	``	``	O	O	O
7	1	Ovah	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	2	heah	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	4	Ty-gah	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
7	5	.	.	O	O	O
7	6	''	''	O	O	O

8	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	1	John	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	2	Powers.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	3	750	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
8	4	words	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	5	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	GLF-RYDER-USNOTES	NNP	O	O	O
9	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
9	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
9	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
9	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
9	6	_	NN	O	O	O
9	7	Much-awaited	NNP	O	B-NP	O
9	8	pairings	NNS	O	I-NP	O
9	9	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
9	10	due	JJ	O	O	O
9	11	Friday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
9	12	;	:	O	O	O
9	13	US	PRP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
9	14	captain	VBP	O	B-VP	B-ProfTitle
9	15	Ben	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	16	Crenshaw	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
9	17	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
9	18	tough	JJ	O	B-NP	O
9	19	call	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	20	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
9	21	make	VB	O	I-VP	O
9	22	;	:	O	O	O
9	23	optimism	NN	O	B-NP	O
9	24	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	25	Davis	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	26	Love	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
9	27	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	1	Joe	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
10	2	Concannon	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
10	3	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	GLF-RYDER-NOTEBOOK	NNP	O	O	O
11	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
11	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
11	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
11	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
11	6	_	NN	O	O	O
11	7	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	8	most	RBS	O	I-NP	O
11	9	popular	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	10	player	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
11	11	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	13	American	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
11	14	team	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	15	again	RB	O	O	O
11	16	draws	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
11	17	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	18	large	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	19	gallery	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	20	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	1	light	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	2	rain	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	3	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
12	4	lots	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	6	large	JJ	O	B-NP	O
12	7	golf	NN	O	I-NP	B-Sport
12	8	umbrellas	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	9	simply	RB	O	O	O
12	10	added	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	11	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
12	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	13	challenge	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	14	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	15	getting	VBG	O	B-VP	O
12	16	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	17	good	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	18	view	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	19	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	1	Shira	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	2	Springer	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	3	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	&	CC	O	O	O
14	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	2	;	:	O	O	O
14	3	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	4	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	5	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	6	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
14	7	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	8	;	:	O	O	O
14	9	&	CC	O	O	O
14	10	QC	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	11	;	:	O	O	O
