0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	11	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	01	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	Editors	NNS	O	O	B-ProfTitle
1	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	2	attention	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	3	managing	VBG	O	O	O
1	4	editors	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
1	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	6	wire	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	7	editors	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
1	8	:	:	O	O	O

2	0	Because	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	1	of	IN	O	I-PP	O
2	2	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
2	3	volume	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	5	The	NNP	O	B-NP	O
2	6	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
2	7	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
2	8	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
2	9	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	10	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	11	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
2	12	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
2	13	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	14	full	JJ	O	B-NP	O
2	15	texts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	16	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	18	Clinton	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	19	grand	JJ	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	20	jury	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	21	testimony	NN	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	22	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
2	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	24	Lewinsky	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	25	testimony	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	26	and	CC	O	O	O
2	27	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	28	rest	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	29	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	30	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	31	Starr	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
2	32	documents	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	33	that	WDT	O	B-NP	O
2	34	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	35	made	VBN	O	I-VP	O
2	36	public	JJ	O	O	O
2	37	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	38	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	39	House	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	40	Judiciary	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	41	Committee	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	42	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	43	morning	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	44	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	Once	RB	O	O	O
3	1	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	2	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
3	3	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	4	electronic	JJ	O	B-NP	O
3	5	form	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	7	The	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	8	Associated	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	9	Press	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
3	10	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
3	11	provide	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	13	full	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	14	texts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	15	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	16	ASCII	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
3	17	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
3	18	HTML	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
3	19	formats	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	20	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	21	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	22	ftp	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	23	site	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	24	and	CC	O	B-PP	O
3	25	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	26	Adobe	NNP	O	B-NP	O
3	27	PDF	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	28	files	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	29	through	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	30	AP	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	31	Send	VB	O	B-VP	O
3	32	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	However	RB	O	O	O
4	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	3	ftp	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	4	site	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	5	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	6	not	RB	O	O	O
4	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	8	same	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	9	site	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	11	AP	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
4	12	used	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	13	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
4	14	deliver	VB	O	I-VP	O
4	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	16	earlier	RBR	O	I-NP	O
4	17	OIC	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	18	report	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	19	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	See	VB	O	B-VP	O
5	1	their	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	2	advisories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	3	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	4	additional	JJ	O	B-NP	O
5	5	information	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	6	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	1	AP	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
6	2	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	3	also	RB	O	I-VP	O
6	4	decided	VBD	O	I-VP	O
6	5	not	RB	O	O	O
6	6	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
6	7	release	VB	O	I-VP	O
6	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	9	full	JJ	O	I-NP	O
6	10	text	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	11	over	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	12	normal	JJ	O	B-NP	O
6	13	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	14	wires	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	15	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Later	RB	O	O	O
7	1	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	3	day	NN	O	I-NP	B-DayFest
7	4	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	5	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
7	6	send	VB	O	I-VP	O
7	7	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	8	complete	JJ	O	I-NP	O
7	9	CLINTON-ADVISORY	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
7	11	advising	VBG	O	B-VP	O
7	12	you	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	14	coverage	NN	O	B-NP	O
7	15	plans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	16	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	17	Tuesday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
7	18	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
7	19	editions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	20	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	21	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	22	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
7	23	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	24	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
7	25	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	&	CC	O	O	O
8	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	2	;	:	O	O	O
8	3	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	4	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
8	5	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
8	6	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
8	7	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
8	8	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
8	9	&	CC	O	O	O
8	10	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	11	;	:	O	O	O
