0	0	1999-09-22	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	14	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	43	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	Sports	NNPS	O	O	O
1	1	stories	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	2	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	3	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	4	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
1	5	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	6	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	7	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	8	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	9	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	10	&	CC	O	O	O
1	11	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	12	;	:	O	O	O
1	13	THURSDAY	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	14	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
1	15	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	16	;	:	O	O	O
1	17	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	18	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	19	23	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
1	20	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	BBN-RHODEN-COLUMN	NNP	O	O	O
2	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	2	Undated	NNP	O	O	O
2	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	4	_	NN	O	O	O
2	5	Sports	NNPS	O	B-NP	O
2	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	7	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	8	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	9	column	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	10	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	12	pivotal	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	13	Mets-Braves	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	14	series	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	15	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	1	William	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
3	2	C.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	3	Rhoden	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	4	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	BBN-METS-BRAVES	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
4	2	Atlanta	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
4	3	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	B-NP	O
4	4	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	5	N.Y.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
4	6	Mets	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
4	7	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	8	Atlanta	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
4	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	10	7	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
4	11	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
4	12	40	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
4	13	p.m.	RB	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
4	14	EDT	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	15	start	VBP	O	B-VP	O
4	16	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	1	Judy	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	2	Battista	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
5	3	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	BBA-YANKS-CHISOX	NNP	O	O	O
6	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
6	2	New	NNP	O	O	B-LocCit
6	3	York	NNP	O	O	I-LocCit
6	4	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
6	5	_	NN	O	O	O
6	6	Chicago	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
6	7	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	9	Yankees	NNPS	O	I-NP	B-OrgTeam
6	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	11	7	CD	O	B-NP	B-NumTime
6	12	:	:	O	O	I-NumTime
6	13	35	CD	O	B-NP	I-NumTime
6	14	p.m.	RB	O	I-NP	I-NumTime
6	15	EDT	NNP	O	I-NP	O
6	16	start	VBP	O	B-VP	O
6	17	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	1	Chris	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	2	Broussard	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	3	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	GLF-RYDER	NNP	O	O	O
8	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
8	2	Brookline	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	4	Mass.	NNP	O	O	O
8	5	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
8	6	_	NN	O	O	O
8	7	Feature	NNP	O	B-NP	O
8	8	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	9	Colin	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	10	Montgomerie	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	12	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
8	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	15	few	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	16	veterans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	17	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	19	European	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
8	20	Ryder	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	21	Cup	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	22	team	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	23	and	CC	O	O	O
8	24	thus	RB	O	O	O
8	25	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	26	pivotal	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	27	person	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	28	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	29	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	30	weekend	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	31	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
8	32	showdown	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	33	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	1	Clifton	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	2	Brown	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
9	3	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	1	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	2	and	CC	O	O	O
10	3	repeats	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
10	4	call	VBP	O	B-VP	O
10	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	6	News	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
10	7	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
10	8	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	9	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
10	10	888	CD	O	O	B-Num
10	11	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
10	12	346-9867	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
10	13	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
10	14	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	I-NP	O
10	15	212	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
10	16	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
10	17	556-1927	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
10	18	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	And	CC	O	O	O
11	1	be	VB	O	B-VP	O
11	2	sure	JJ	O	O	O
11	3	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
11	4	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	5	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	6	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
11	7	sports	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	8	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	10	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
11	11	partners	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	12	:	:	O	O	O
11	13	Bloomberg	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
11	14	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
11	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	16	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	17	Boston	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	18	Globe	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	20	Cox	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
11	21	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	22	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	23	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
11	24	Hearst	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
11	25	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	26	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	28	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	29	Arizona	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocStat
11	30	Republic	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocStat
11	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	32	Kansas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
11	33	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
11	34	Star	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	35	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	36	Fort	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
11	37	Worth	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
11	38	Star-Telegram	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
11	39	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	40	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
11	41	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
11	42	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	43	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
11	44	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	45	San	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
11	46	Francisco	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	47	Chronicle	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	48	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
11	49	Seattle	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
11	50	Post-Intelligencer	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
11	51	.	.	O	O	O
