0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	13	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	24	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	2	two	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
1	3	articles	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	5	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
1	6	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
1	7	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
1	8	excerpted	VBN	O	I-VP	O
1	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	10	recent	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	11	issues	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	13	Discover	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	14	magazine	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	16	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
1	17	available	JJ	O	O	O
1	18	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	19	one-shot	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	20	purchase	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	21	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	22	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	23	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
1	24	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	25	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
1	26	Syndicate	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	27	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	ALL	NNP	O	O	B-Money
2	1	THE	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	2	ART	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	3	IS	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
2	4	FREE	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	5	OF	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
2	6	CHARGE	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
2	7	!	NN	O	O	O

3	0	-	:	O	O	O
3	1	-	:	O	O	O
3	2	-	:	O	O	O
3	3	-	:	O	O	O
3	4	-	:	O	O	O
3	5	-	:	O	O	O
3	6	-	:	O	O	O
3	7	-	:	O	O	O
3	8	-	:	O	O	O
3	9	-	:	O	O	O
3	10	-	:	O	O	O
3	11	-	:	O	O	O
3	12	-	:	O	O	O
3	13	-	:	O	O	O
3	14	-	:	O	O	O
3	15	-	:	O	O	O
3	16	-	:	O	O	O
3	17	-	:	O	O	O
3	18	-	:	O	O	O
3	19	-	:	O	O	O
3	20	-	:	O	O	O
3	21	-	:	O	O	O
3	22	-	:	O	O	O
3	23	-	:	O	O	O
3	24	-	:	O	O	O
3	25	-	:	O	O	O
3	26	-	:	O	O	O
3	27	-	:	O	O	O
3	28	-	:	O	O	O
3	29	-	:	O	O	O
3	30	-	:	O	O	O
3	31	-	:	O	O	O
3	32	-	:	O	O	O
3	33	-	:	O	O	O
3	34	-	:	O	O	O
3	35	-	:	O	O	O
3	36	-	:	O	O	O
3	37	-	:	O	O	O
3	38	-	:	O	O	O
3	39	-	:	O	O	O
3	40	-	:	O	O	O
3	41	-	:	O	O	O
3	42	-	:	O	O	O
3	43	-	:	O	O	O
3	44	-	:	O	O	O
3	45	-	:	O	O	O
3	46	-	:	O	O	O
3	47	-	:	O	O	O
3	48	-	:	O	O	O
3	49	-	:	O	O	O
3	50	-	:	O	O	O
3	51	-	:	O	O	O
3	52	-	:	O	O	O
3	53	-	:	O	O	O
3	54	-	:	O	O	O

4	0	ASK	NNP	O	O	O
4	1	OUR	PP$	O	O	O
4	2	SALES	NNS	O	O	O
4	3	STAFF	NNP	O	O	O
4	4	ABOUT	NNP	O	O	O
4	5	SUBSCRIBING	NNP	O	O	O
4	6	TO	TO	O	B-PP	O
4	7	DISCOVER	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
4	8	NEWS	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	9	SERVICE	NNP	O	I-NP	O
4	10	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	Each	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	1	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
5	3	clients	NNS	O	B-NP	O
5	4	receive	VBP	O	B-VP	O
5	5	two	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
5	6	articles	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	7	-	:	O	O	O
5	8	-	:	O	O	O
5	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	10	both	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	11	Spanish	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LangRace
5	12	and	CC	O	O	O
5	13	English	JJ	O	O	B-LangRace
5	14	-	:	O	O	O
5	15	-	:	O	O	O
5	16	plus	CC	O	O	O
5	17	eye-catching	JJ	O	B-NP	O
5	18	art	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	19	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
5	20	brighten	VB	O	I-VP	O
5	21	their	PP$	O	B-NP	O
5	22	pages	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	23	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	-	:	O	O	O
6	1	-	:	O	O	O
6	2	-	:	O	O	O
6	3	-	:	O	O	O
6	4	-	:	O	O	O
6	5	-	:	O	O	O
6	6	-	:	O	O	O
6	7	-	:	O	O	O
6	8	-	:	O	O	O
6	9	-	:	O	O	O
6	10	-	:	O	O	O
6	11	-	:	O	O	O
6	12	-	:	O	O	O
6	13	-	:	O	O	O
6	14	-	:	O	O	O
6	15	-	:	O	O	O
6	16	-	:	O	O	O
6	17	-	:	O	O	O
6	18	-	:	O	O	O
6	19	-	:	O	O	O
6	20	-	:	O	O	O
6	21	-	:	O	O	O
6	22	-	:	O	O	O
6	23	-	:	O	O	O
6	24	-	:	O	O	O
6	25	-	:	O	O	O
6	26	-	:	O	O	O
6	27	-	:	O	O	O
6	28	-	:	O	O	O
6	29	-	:	O	O	O
6	30	-	:	O	O	O
6	31	-	:	O	O	O
6	32	-	:	O	O	O
6	33	-	:	O	O	O
6	34	-	:	O	O	O
6	35	-	:	O	O	O
6	36	-	:	O	O	O
6	37	-	:	O	O	O
6	38	-	:	O	O	O
6	39	-	:	O	O	O
6	40	-	:	O	O	O
6	41	-	:	O	O	O
6	42	-	:	O	O	O
6	43	-	:	O	O	O
6	44	-	:	O	O	O
6	45	-	:	O	O	O
6	46	-	:	O	O	O
6	47	-	:	O	O	O
6	48	-	:	O	O	O
6	49	-	:	O	O	O
6	50	-	:	O	O	O
6	51	-	:	O	O	O
6	52	-	:	O	O	O
6	53	-	:	O	O	O
6	54	-	:	O	O	O

7	0	&	CC	O	O	O
7	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	2	;	:	O	O	O
7	3	NEEDLES	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	4	AND	CC	O	I-NP	O
7	5	NERVES	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
7	6	&	CC	O	I-NP	I-Org
7	7	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
7	8	;	:	O	O	I-Org
7	9	&	CC	O	O	I-Org
7	10	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	11	;	:	O	O	I-Org
7	12	&	CC	O	O	I-Org
7	13	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	14	;	:	O	O	I-Org
7	15	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	I-Org
7	16	1COMMA500	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	17	words	NNS	O	I-NP	I-Org
7	18	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	I-Org
7	19	&	CC	O	O	I-Org
7	20	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	21	;	:	O	O	I-Org
7	22	&	CC	O	O	I-Org
7	23	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	24	;	:	O	O	I-Org
7	25	FOUR	NNP	O	B-NP	I-Org
7	26	COLOR	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
7	27	SLIDES	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
7	28	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
7	29	QL	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	30	;	:	O	O	O
7	31	&	CC	O	O	O
7	32	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	33	;	:	O	O	O
7	34	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	35	CATHERINE	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	36	DOLD	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
7	37	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
7	38	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	39	;	:	O	O	O
7	40	&	CC	O	O	O
7	41	QC	NNP	O	B-NP	O
7	42	;	:	O	O	O

8	0	Five	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
8	1	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
8	2	ago	IN	O	O	O
8	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	4	physicist	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
8	5	Zang-Hee	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
8	6	Cho	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	7	sought	VBD	O	B-VP	O
8	8	help	NN	O	B-NP	O
8	9	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	10	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	11	acupuncturist	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
8	12	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	13	relief	NN	O	B-NP	O
8	14	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	15	excruciating	VBG	O	B-VP	O
8	16	back	NN	O	B-NP	O
8	17	pain	NN	O	I-NP	O
8	18	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	Initially	RB	O	O	O
9	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	2	Cho	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	3	scoffed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	4	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	6	idea	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	7	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	8	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	9	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	10	educated	VBN	O	I-NP	O
9	11	person	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	13	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
9	14	says	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
9	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	16	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
9	17	didn	NN	O	B-NP	O
9	18	't	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	19	believe	VB	O	B-VP	O
9	20	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	21	acupuncture	NN	O	B-NP	B-Medical
9	22	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	But	CC	O	O	O
10	1	much	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	2	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
10	3	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
10	4	surprise	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	6	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
10	7	worked	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	8	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	How	WRB	O	O	O
11	1	could	MD	O	O	O
11	2	inserting	VBG	O	O	O
11	3	needles	NNS	O	B-NP	O
11	4	into	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	5	seemingly	RB	O	B-NP	O
11	6	random	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	7	points	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	8	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	10	body	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	11	possibly	RB	O	B-VP	O
11	12	affect	VBP	O	I-VP	O
11	13	human	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Animal
11	14	health	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	15	?	.	O	O	O

12	0	Read	NNP	O	O	B-Peop
12	1	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	2	Cho	NNP	O	B-NP	O
12	3	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
12	4	subsequent	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	5	study	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	6	involving	VBG	O	B-VP	O
12	7	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	8	traditional	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	9	Chinese	JJ	O	I-NP	B-LangRace
12	10	medicine	NN	O	I-NP	B-Medical
12	11	and	CC	O	O	O
12	12	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	13	few	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	14	student	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
12	15	volunteers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	16	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	17	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	18	feature	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	19	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	20	Discover	NNP	O	B-NP	O
12	21	magazine	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	22	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	Catherine	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	1	Dold	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
13	2	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
13	3	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	4	free-lance	JJ	O	I-NP	O
13	5	writer	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
13	6	who	WP	O	B-NP	O
13	7	lives	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
13	8	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	9	Boulder	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
13	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	11	Colo	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
13	12	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	SLUGGED	NNP	O	B-NP	O
14	1	:	:	O	O	O
14	2	BC-WONDERS-OF-ACUPUNCTURE-NYTSF	NNP	O	B-NP	O

15	0	SENT	NNP	O	B-NP	O
15	1	TO	TO	O	O	O
15	2	:	:	O	O	O
15	3	category	NN	O	B-NP	O
15	4	codes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
15	5	``	``	O	I-NP	O
15	6	l	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	7	''	''	O	I-NP	O
15	8	lifestyle	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	9	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	10	and	CC	O	O	O
15	11	``	``	O	O	O
15	12	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	13	''	''	O	I-NP	O
15	14	general	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
15	15	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	16	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	&	CC	O	O	O
16	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	2	;	:	O	O	O
16	3	AN	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	4	OCEAN	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	5	OF	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	6	SELTZER	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	7	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
16	8	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	9	;	:	O	O	O
16	10	&	CC	O	O	O
16	11	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	12	;	:	O	O	O
16	13	&	CC	O	O	O
16	14	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	15	;	:	O	O	O
16	16	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
16	17	700	CD	O	O	B-Num
16	18	words	NNS	O	O	O
16	19	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
16	20	&	CC	O	O	O
16	21	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	22	;	:	O	O	O
16	23	&	CC	O	O	O
16	24	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	25	;	:	O	O	O
16	26	ONE	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
16	27	B	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	28	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
16	29	AMP	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	30	;	:	O	O	O
16	31	W	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	32	SLIDE	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	33	&	CC	O	O	O
16	34	QL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	35	;	:	O	O	O
16	36	&	CC	O	O	O
16	37	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	38	;	:	O	O	O
16	39	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
16	40	KATHY	NNP	O	B-VP	O
16	41	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	42	SVITIL	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
16	43	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
16	44	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
16	45	;	:	O	O	O
16	46	&	CC	O	O	O
16	47	QC	NNP	O	B-NP	O
16	48	;	:	O	O	O

17	0	Jupiter	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
17	1	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
17	2	moon	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	3	Europa	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
17	4	continues	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
17	5	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
17	6	surprise	VB	O	I-VP	O
17	7	scientists	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
17	8	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	First	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Num
18	1	there	RB	O	O	O
18	2	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	3	evidence	NN	O	B-NP	O
18	4	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	5	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	6	ocean	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	7	beneath	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	8	miles	NNS	O	B-NP	B-NumUnit
18	9	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	10	ice	NN	O	B-NP	O
18	11	.	.	O	O	O

19	0	Now	RB	O	O	O
19	1	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
19	2	appears	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
19	3	that	IN	O	O	O
19	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
19	5	ocean	NN	O	I-NP	O
19	6	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
19	7	carbonated	VBN	O	I-VP	O
19	8	.	.	O	O	O

20	0	Kathy	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
20	1	A.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
20	2	Svitil	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
20	3	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
20	4	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	5	associate	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
20	6	editor	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
20	7	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	8	Discover	NNP	O	B-NP	O
20	9	magazine	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	10	.	.	O	O	O

21	0	SLUGGED	NNP	O	B-NP	O
21	1	:	:	O	O	O
21	2	BC-OCEAN-OF-SELTZER-NYTSF	NNP	O	B-NP	O

22	0	SENT	NNP	O	B-NP	O
22	1	TO	TO	O	O	O
22	2	:	:	O	O	O
22	3	category	NN	O	B-NP	O
22	4	codes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	5	``	``	O	O	O
22	6	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	7	''	''	O	I-NP	O
22	8	general	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
22	9	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	10	and	CC	O	O	O
22	11	``	``	O	B-NP	O
22	12	l	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	13	''	''	O	I-NP	O
22	14	lifestyle	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	15	news	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	16	.	.	O	O	O

23	0	&	CC	O	O	O
23	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
23	2	;	:	O	O	O
23	3	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
23	4	purchase	VBP	O	B-VP	O
23	5	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
23	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
23	7	contact	NN	O	B-NP	O
23	8	one	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
23	9	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
23	10	these	DT	O	B-NP	O
23	11	New	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
23	12	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
23	13	Times	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
23	14	Syndicate	NNP	O	I-NP	O
23	15	sales	NNS	O	I-NP	O
23	16	representatives	NNS	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
23	17	:	:	O	O	O
23	18	&	CC	O	O	O
23	19	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
23	20	;	:	O	O	O

24	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
24	1	_	NN	O	O	O
24	2	U.S.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
24	3	and	CC	O	O	O
24	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
24	5	Pacific	NNP	O	I-NP	O
24	6	:	:	O	O	O
24	7	CONNIE	NNP	O	B-NP	O
24	8	WHITE	NNP	O	I-NP	O
24	9	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
24	10	Kansas	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
24	11	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
24	12	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
24	13	1-800-444-0267	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
24	14	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
24	15	816-822-8448	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
24	16	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
24	17	or	CC	O	O	O
24	18	fax	NN	O	B-NP	O
24	19	her	PP$	O	O	O
24	20	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
24	21	816-822-1444	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
24	22	.	.	O	O	O

25	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
25	1	_	NN	O	O	O
25	2	Europe	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
25	3	and	CC	O	O	O
25	4	Asia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
25	5	:	:	O	O	O
25	6	KARL	NNP	O	B-NP	O
25	7	HORWITZ	NNP	O	I-NP	O
25	8	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
25	9	Paris	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
25	10	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
25	11	47-42-17-11	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
25	12	;	:	O	O	O
25	13	fax	NN	O	B-NP	O
25	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
25	15	47-42-80-44	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
25	16	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
25	17	47-42-18-81	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
25	18	;	:	O	O	O
25	19	telex	NN	O	B-NP	O
25	20	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
25	21	282-942.	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
25	22	&	CC	O	O	O
25	23	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
25	24	;	:	O	O	O

26	0	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
26	1	_	NN	O	O	O
26	2	Latin	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LangRace
26	3	America	NNP	O	I-NP	O
26	4	:	:	O	O	O
26	5	OLIVIA	NNP	O	B-NP	O
26	6	VASQUEZ	NNP	O	I-NP	O
26	7	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
26	8	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
26	9	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
26	10	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
26	11	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
26	12	310	CD	O	O	B-Num
26	13	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
26	14	996-0075	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
26	15	;	:	O	O	O
26	16	fax	NN	O	B-NP	O
26	17	:	:	O	O	O
26	18	310-996-0089	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
26	19	.	.	O	O	O

27	0	Many	JJ	O	B-NP	O
27	1	Thanks	NNS	O	I-NP	O
27	2	!	NN	O	O	O

28	0	The	DT	O	O	O
28	1	New	NNP	O	O	B-OrgCorp
28	2	York	NNP	O	O	I-OrgCorp
28	3	Times	NNP	O	O	I-OrgCorp
28	4	Syndicate	NNP	O	O	O

29	0	&	CC	O	O	O
29	1	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
29	2	;	:	O	O	O
29	3	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
29	4	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
29	5	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
29	6	headquarters	NN	O	I-NP	O
29	7	:	:	O	O	O
29	8	212-499-3300	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
29	9	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
29	10	1-800-972-3550	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
29	11	;	:	O	O	O
29	12	fax	NN	O	B-NP	O
29	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
29	14	212-499-3382.	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
29	15	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	I-NP	O
29	16	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
29	17	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
29	18	;	:	O	O	O
