0	0	1998-09-22	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
0	1	17	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	11	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	A	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	partial	JJ	O	I-NP	O
1	2	list	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	3	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	4	U.S.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
1	5	agencies	NNS	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
1	6	accepting	VBG	O	B-VP	O
1	7	donations	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	8	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
1	9	fight	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	11	famine	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	12	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	13	Sudan	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
1	14	:	:	O	O	O

2	0	Action	NNP	O	B-NP	O
2	1	Against	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	2	Hunger	NNP	O	O	O

3	0	875	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	1	Sixth	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Num
3	2	Ave.	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	4	Suite	NNP	O	O	O
3	5	1905	CD	O	O	B-Date

4	0	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
4	1	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
4	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	3	NY	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
4	4	10001	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

5	0	212-967-7800	CD	O	O	B-Num

6	0	American	NNP	O	O	B-LangRace
6	1	Jewish	JJ	O	O	B-Religion
6	2	World	NNP	O	O	B-Org
6	3	Service	NNP	O	O	I-Org

7	0	989	CD	O	O	B-Num
7	1	Avenue	NNP	O	O	O
7	2	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	3	the	DT	O	O	O
7	4	AmericasCOMMA	NNP	O	O	O

8	0	10th	JJ	O	O	B-Num
8	1	floor	NN	O	O	O

9	0	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
9	1	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
9	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	3	NY	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
9	4	10018	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

10	0	212-736-2597	CD	O	O	B-Num

11	0	American	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
11	1	Red	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
11	2	Cross	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp

12	0	ARC	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
12	1	International	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	2	Response	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	3	Fund	NNP	O	I-NP	O

13	0	P.O.	NNP	O	B-NP	O
13	1	Box	NNP	O	I-NP	O
13	2	37243	CD	O	I-NP	B-NumZip

14	0	Washington	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
14	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
14	2	DC	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
14	3	20013	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

15	0	1-800-HELP	NN	O	O	B-Num
15	1	NOW	RB	O	O	O

16	0	CARE	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
16	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
16	2	Sudan	NNP	O	O	B-LocCoun
16	3	Famine	NN	O	O	O
16	4	Relief	NNP	O	O	O

17	0	151	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
17	1	Ellis	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
17	2	St.	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
17	3	N.E	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
17	4	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	Atlanta	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
18	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
18	2	GA	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
18	3	30303	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

19	0	404-681-2552	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
19	1	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
19	2	1-800-422-7385	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num

20	0	Catholic	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Religion
20	1	Relief	NNP	O	I-NP	O
20	2	Services	NNPS	O	I-NP	O

21	0	209	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
21	1	West	NNP	O	I-NP	O
21	2	Fayette	NNP	O	I-NP	O
21	3	St	NNP	O	I-NP	O
21	4	.	.	O	O	O

22	0	Baltimore	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
22	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
22	2	MD	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
22	3	21201-3443	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

23	0	410-625-2220	CD	O	O	B-Num

24	0	Doctors	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
24	1	Without	IN	O	B-PP	O
24	2	Borders	NNPS	O	B-NP	O

25	0	6	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
25	1	East	NNP	O	I-NP	O
25	2	39th	NN	O	I-NP	B-Num
25	3	St.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
25	4	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
25	5	8th	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Num
25	6	floor	NN	O	I-NP	O

26	0	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
26	1	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
26	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
26	3	NY	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
26	4	10016	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

27	0	212-679-6800	CD	O	O	B-Num

28	0	MAP	NNP	O	O	O
28	1	International	NNP	O	O	O

29	0	2200	CD	O	O	B-Date
29	1	Glynco	NNP	O	O	O
29	2	Parkway	NNP	O	O	B-OrgCorp

30	0	P.O.	NNP	O	B-NP	O
30	1	Box	NNP	O	I-NP	O
30	2	215000	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num

31	0	Brunswick	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
31	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
31	2	GA	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
31	3	31521	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

32	0	912-265-6010	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
32	1	or	CC	O	I-NP	O
32	2	1-800-225-8550	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num

33	0	Oxfam	NNP	O	O	O
33	1	America	NNP	O	O	O

34	0	26	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
34	1	West	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
34	2	St	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
34	3	.	.	O	O	O

35	0	Boston	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
35	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
35	2	MA	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
35	3	02111-1206	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

36	0	1-800-77-OXFAM	NN	O	O	B-Num

37	0	Save	NNP	O	B-VP	O
37	1	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
37	2	Children	NNP	O	I-NP	O

38	0	54	CD	O	O	B-Num
38	1	Wilton	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
38	2	Road	NNP	O	O	I-Loc

39	0	Westport	NNP	O	B-NP	O
39	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
39	2	CT	NN	O	O	B-LocStat
39	3	06880	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

40	0	203-221-4000	CD	O	O	B-Num

41	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
41	1	U.S.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
41	2	Committee	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
41	3	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
41	4	UNICEF	NNP	O	B-VP	O

42	0	333	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
42	1	East	NNP	O	I-NP	O
42	2	38th	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Num
42	3	St	NNP	O	I-NP	O
42	4	.	.	O	O	O

43	0	New	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
43	1	York	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
43	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
43	3	NY	NNP	O	O	B-LocStat
43	4	10016	CD	O	O	B-NumZip

44	0	1-800-FOR-KIDS	JJ	O	O	B-Num

45	0	Story	NNP	O	O	O
45	1	Filed	NNP	O	O	O
45	2	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
45	3	Cox	NNP	O	O	O
45	4	Newspapers	NNP	O	O	O

