0	0	1999-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	01	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	00	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	MANN	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
0	5	THEATRES	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	6	CONSIDERS	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	7	PULLING	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	8	CURTAIN	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	9	ON	IN	O	O	I-Org
0	10	SOME	DT	O	O	I-Org
0	11	LOCATIONS	NNP	O	O	I-Org

1	0	LOS	NNP	O	O	O
1	1	ANGELES	NNP	O	O	O
1	2	_	NN	O	O	O
1	3	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	4	parent	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	7	struggling	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	8	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	9	Theatres	NNP	O	I-NP	O
1	10	chain	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	12	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
1	13	recently	RB	O	O	O
1	14	filed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
1	15	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	16	Chapter	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	17	11	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
1	18	bankruptcy	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	19	protection	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	20	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	21	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
1	22	Monday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	23	that	IN	O	O	O
1	24	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
1	25	might	MD	O	O	O
1	26	close	VB	O	O	O
1	27	underperforming	VBG	O	O	O
1	28	locations	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	29	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	``	``	O	O	O
2	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
2	2	're	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	3	going	VBG	O	I-VP	O
2	4	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
2	5	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	6	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	8	overall	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	9	business	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	10	and	CC	O	O	O
2	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	12	viability	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	14	all	PDT	O	B-NP	O
2	15	the	DT	O	I-NP	O
2	16	assetsCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	17	''	''	O	O	O
2	18	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	19	Michael	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
2	20	Solomon	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
2	21	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	22	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	23	turnaround	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	24	specialist	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	25	named	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	26	last	JJ	O	B-NP	O
2	27	week	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	28	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
2	29	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	30	post	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	31	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	32	chief	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	33	executive	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	34	officer	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	35	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	36	WestStar	NNP	O	B-NP	O
2	37	Cinemas	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	38	Inc	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	39	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	``	``	O	O	O
3	1	One	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	2	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	4	beauties	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	6	filing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
3	7	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	8	Chapter	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	9	11	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
3	10	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	11	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	12	now	RB	O	O	O
3	13	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
3	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	15	time	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	16	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	17	look	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	18	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	19	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	20	options	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	21	.	.	O	O	O
3	22	''	''	O	O	O

4	0	Solomon	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	2	no	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	3	timetable	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	4	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	5	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	6	set	VBN	O	I-VP	O
4	7	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	8	possible	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	9	closures	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	10	or	CC	O	O	O
4	11	filing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
4	12	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	13	reorganization	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	14	plan	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	15	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	17	bankruptcy	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	18	court	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	19	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	He	PRP	O	B-NP	O
5	1	plans	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
5	2	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
5	3	seek	VB	O	I-VP	O
5	4	renegotiation	NN	O	B-NP	O
5	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	6	lease	VBP	O	B-VP	O
5	7	agreements	NNS	O	B-NP	O
5	8	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	9	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
5	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	I-Org
5	11	which	WDT	O	B-NP	I-Org
5	12	operates	VBZ	O	B-VP	I-Org
5	13	54	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
5	14	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	15	with	IN	O	B-PP	I-Org
5	16	357	CD	O	B-NP	I-Org
5	17	screens	NNS	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	18	including	VBG	O	B-PP	I-Org
5	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	I-Org
5	20	legendary	JJ	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	21	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	22	Chinese	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
5	23	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	24	Hollywood	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
5	25	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	Encino-based	VBN	O	O	O
6	1	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
6	2	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	3	lagged	VBN	O	I-VP	O
6	4	rivals	NNS	O	B-NP	O
6	5	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	6	building	VBG	O	B-VP	O
6	7	megaplex	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	8	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	9	that	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	10	cater	VBP	O	B-VP	O
6	11	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
6	12	customers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
6	13	'	POS	O	B-NP	O
6	14	preference	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	15	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	16	multiple	JJ	O	B-NP	O
6	17	screens	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	18	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	19	tiered	JJ	O	B-NP	O
6	20	seating	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	21	and	CC	O	O	O
6	22	staggered	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	23	start	VBP	O	B-VP	O
6	24	times	NNS	O	B-NP	O
6	25	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
7	1	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
7	2	only	RB	O	O	O
7	3	megaplex	NN	O	O	O
7	4	among	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	5	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
7	6	27	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
7	7	Southern	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
7	8	California	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Loc
7	9	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	I-Loc
7	10	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	12	9-month-old	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
7	13	Plant	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Plant
7	14	16	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
7	15	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	16	Panorama	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
7	17	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
7	18	and	CC	O	O	O
7	19	analysts	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
7	20	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
7	21	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
7	22	warning	VBG	O	I-VP	O
7	23	that	IN	O	O	O
7	24	outmoded	JJ	O	B-NP	O
7	25	multiplexes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	26	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
7	27	creating	VBG	O	I-VP	O
7	28	cash-flow	JJ	O	B-NP	O
7	29	problems	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	30	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	31	operators	NNS	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
7	32	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
8	1	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
8	2	other	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	3	local	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	4	sites	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	5	include	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	7	six-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	8	Agoura	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	9	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
8	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	12	Village	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	13	8	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
8	14	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	15	Westlake	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	16	Village	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	17	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	19	eight-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	20	Janss	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	21	Marketplace	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	22	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	23	Thousand	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
8	24	Oaks	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
8	25	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	26	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	27	four-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	28	Buenaventura	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	29	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	30	Ventura	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	32	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	33	five-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	34	Simi	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	35	Valley	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	36	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	37	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	38	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	39	Marketplace	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	40	4	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
8	41	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	42	Glendale	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
8	43	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	44	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	45	10-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
8	46	Exchange	NNP	O	I-NP	O
8	47	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	48	Glendale	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
8	49	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	50	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	51	nine-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	52	Valley	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
8	53	West	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
8	54	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
8	55	Tarzana	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
8	56	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
8	57	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	58	eight-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	59	Granada	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
8	60	Hills	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	61	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
8	62	and	CC	O	O	O
8	63	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
8	64	seven-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
8	65	Mann	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
8	66	Valencia	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
8	67	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	Solomon	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	3	bankruptcy	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	4	filing	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	6	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
9	7	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
9	8	have	VB	O	I-VP	O
9	9	no	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	10	immediate	JJ	O	I-NP	O
9	11	impact	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	12	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	13	operations	NNS	O	B-NP	O
9	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	15	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	16	necessary	JJ	O	O	O
9	17	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	18	order	NN	O	B-NP	O
9	19	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	20	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	21	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
9	22	remain	VB	O	I-VP	O
9	23	competitive	JJ	O	O	O
9	24	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	``	``	O	O	O
10	1	As	IN	O	O	O
10	2	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
10	3	industry	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	4	continues	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
10	5	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
10	6	change	VB	O	I-VP	O
10	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	9	expense	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	10	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	11	retrofitting	NN	O	B-NP	O
10	12	older	JJR	O	O	O
10	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	14	traditionally	RB	O	O	O
10	15	formatted	VBD	O	O	O
10	16	theaters	NNS	O	B-NP	O
10	17	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	18	state-of-the-art	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	19	technology	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	20	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
10	21	increased	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	22	dramaticallyCOMMA	NN	O	O	O
10	23	''	''	O	O	O
10	24	Solomon	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
10	25	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
10	26	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	``	``	O	O	O
11	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
11	2	believe	VBP	O	B-VP	O
11	3	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
11	4	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
11	5	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	7	best	JJS	O	I-NP	O
11	8	interests	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	9	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	10	all	PDT	O	B-NP	O
11	11	our	PP$	O	I-NP	O
11	12	constituents	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	13	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
11	14	complete	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	15	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	16	strategic	JJ	O	I-NP	O
11	17	restructuring	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	18	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	20	company	NN	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
11	21	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
11	22	thereby	RB	O	B-VP	O
11	23	improving	VBG	O	I-VP	O
11	24	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
11	25	financing	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	26	structure	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	27	and	CC	O	O	O
11	28	creating	VBG	O	B-VP	O
11	29	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	30	opportunity	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	31	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	32	capital	NN	O	B-NP	O
11	33	infusion	NN	O	I-NP	B-Medical
11	34	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
11	35	make	VB	O	I-VP	O
11	36	upgrades	NNS	O	B-NP	O
11	37	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
11	38	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
11	39	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	40	.	.	O	O	O
11	41	''	''	O	O	O

12	0	WestStar	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
12	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	2	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	3	affiliate	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	4	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	5	Wall	NNP	O	B-NP	O
12	6	Street	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	7	investment	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	8	bank	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	9	Warburg	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	10	Dillon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
12	11	Read	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
12	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	13	listed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	14	assets	NNS	O	B-NP	O
12	15	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
12	16	debts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	17	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	18	more	RBR	O	B-NP	O
12	19	than	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	20	$100	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
12	21	million	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
12	22	each	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	23	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	24	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	25	filing	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	26	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	27	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	28	U.S.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCoun
12	29	Bankruptcy	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
12	30	Court	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
12	31	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	32	Wilmington	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
12	33	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	34	Del	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
12	35	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	It	PRP	O	B-NP	O
13	1	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
13	2	obtained	VBN	O	I-VP	O
13	3	up	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	4	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
13	5	$15	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
13	6	million	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
13	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	8	debtor-in-possession	NN	O	B-NP	O
13	9	financing	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	10	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	11	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	12	group	NN	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
13	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	14	creditors	NNS	O	B-NP	O
13	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
13	16	led	VBN	O	B-VP	O
13	17	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	18	Canadian	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
13	19	Imperial	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
13	20	Bank	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
13	21	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	``	``	O	O	O
14	1	With	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	2	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
14	3	DIP	NNP	O	I-NP	O
14	4	financing	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	5	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	6	place	NN	O	B-NP	O
14	7	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
14	8	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
14	9	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
14	10	confident	JJ	O	O	O
14	11	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
14	12	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
14	13	have	VB	O	I-VP	O
14	14	adequate	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Medical
14	15	financial	JJ	O	I-NP	O
14	16	resources	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	17	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
14	18	continue	VB	O	I-VP	O
14	19	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
14	20	operate	VB	O	I-VP	O
14	21	uninterrupted	JJ	O	O	O
14	22	during	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
14	24	reorganization	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	25	processCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	26	''	''	O	I-NP	O
14	27	Solomon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
14	28	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
14	29	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	Warburg	NNP	O	B-NP	O
15	1	Pincus	NNP	O	I-NP	O
15	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	3	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
15	4	bought	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	6	chain	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	7	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	8	1997	CD	O	B-NP	B-Date
15	9	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	10	$165	NN	O	B-NP	B-Money
15	11	million	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
15	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
15	13	put	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	14	Mann	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
15	15	up	IN	O	O	O
15	16	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	17	sale	NN	O	B-NP	O
15	18	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	19	January	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
15	20	but	CC	O	O	O
15	21	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	22	unable	JJ	O	O	O
15	23	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
15	24	find	VB	O	I-VP	O
15	25	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	26	buyer	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
15	27	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	Solomon	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
16	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
16	2	his	PP$	O	O	O
16	3	major	JJ	O	B-NP	O
16	4	task	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	5	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
16	6	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
16	7	be	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	8	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
16	9	sell	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	10	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	11	company	NN	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	12	but	CC	O	O	O
16	13	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
16	14	improve	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	15	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
16	16	performance	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	17	so	IN	O	O	O
16	18	that	IN	O	O	O
16	19	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
16	20	sale	NN	O	I-NP	O
16	21	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
16	22	be	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	23	more	RBR	O	O	O
16	24	viable	JJ	O	O	O
16	25	.	.	O	O	O

17	0	Declining	VBG	O	B-NP	O
17	1	box	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	2	office	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	3	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	4	older	JJR	O	B-NP	O
17	5	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	O
17	6	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
17	7	led	VBN	O	I-VP	O
17	8	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
17	9	owners	NNS	O	B-NP	O
17	10	closing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
17	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	12	Americana	NNS	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
17	13	5	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
17	14	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	15	Panorama	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
17	16	City	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
17	17	and	CC	O	O	O
17	18	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	19	six-screen	JJ	O	I-NP	O
17	20	UA	NNP	O	I-NP	O
17	21	Warner	NNP	O	I-NP	O
17	22	Center	NNP	O	I-NP	O
17	23	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	24	Woodland	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
17	25	Hills	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
17	26	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	27	summer	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	28	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	General	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
18	1	Cinemas	NNP	O	I-NP	O
18	2	recently	RB	O	O	O
18	3	announced	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	4	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
18	5	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
18	6	seeking	VBG	O	I-VP	O
18	7	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
18	8	sell	VB	O	I-VP	O
18	9	its	PP$	O	O	O
18	10	six	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
18	11	Los	NNP	O	I-NP	O
18	12	Angeles-area	JJ	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
18	13	theaters	NNS	O	I-NP	O
18	14	.	.	O	O	O
