0	0	2000-09-22	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	19	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	28	CD	O	O	I-Num

1	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	1	Los	NNP	O	I-NP	B-LocCit
1	2	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
1	3	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	4	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	5	plans	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	6	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
1	7	move	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	9	following	VBG	O	I-NP	O
1	10	general	JJ	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
1	11	stories	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	12	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	13	use	VBP	O	B-NP	O
1	14	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	15	NYTimes	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
1	16	News	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	17	Service	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	18	clients	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	19	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
1	20	AMs	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	21	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
1	22	PMs	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	23	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	24	Saturday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	25	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	26	Sept.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
1	27	23	CD	O	I-NP	I-Date
1	28	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	29	and	CC	O	O	O
1	30	thereafter	RB	O	O	O
1	31	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	For	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	1	questions	NNS	O	B-NP	O
2	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	3	contact	NN	O	B-NP	O
2	4	Gerry	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
2	5	Hoppe	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
2	6	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	8	Daily	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	9	News	NNP	O	I-NP	O
2	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	11	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
2	12	818	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	13	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
2	14	713-3702	CD	O	O	B-Num
2	15	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	LITTON-MERGE	NNP	O	O	O
3	1	-LBR-	-LBR-	O	O	O
3	2	Los	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCit
3	3	Angeles	NNP	O	I-NP	I-LocCit
3	4	-RBR-	-RBR-	O	O	O
3	5	-	:	O	O	O
3	6	-	:	O	O	O
3	7	Litton	NNP	O	B-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	8	Industries	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
3	9	Inc	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
3	10	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	11	Friday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
3	12	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	13	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
3	14	merge	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	15	its	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	16	Agoura	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	17	Hills-based	NNP	O	I-NP	O
3	18	Data	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	19	Systems	NNPS	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
3	20	Division	NNP	O	I-NP	I-OrgCorp
3	21	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	22	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
3	23	employs	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	24	600	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
3	25	people	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	26	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	27	into	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	28	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	29	Northridge	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
3	30	plant	NN	O	I-NP	B-Plant
3	31	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	By	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	1	Jesse	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	2	Hiestand	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
4	3	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	X	NNP	O	O	O
5	1	X	NNP	O	O	O
5	2	X	NNP	O	O	O
