0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	16	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	06	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	ENCINO	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
0	5	ACTOR	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	6	CONVINCING	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	7	AS	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	8	THE	DT	O	O	O
0	9	LATE	JJ	O	O	B-Org
0	10	JACK	NNP	O	O	I-Org
0	11	BENNY	NNP	O	O	I-Org

1	0	LOS	NNP	O	O	B-Loc
1	1	ANGELES	NNP	O	O	I-Loc
1	2	_	NN	O	O	O
1	3	&	CC	O	O	O
1	4	UR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	5	;	:	O	O	O
1	6	&	CC	O	O	O
1	7	LR	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	8	;	:	O	O	O
1	9	It	PRP	O	B-NP	O
1	10	's	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	11	uncanny	JJ	O	O	O
1	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	13	even	RB	O	B-NP	O
1	14	a	DT	O	I-NP	O
1	15	little	JJ	O	I-NP	O
1	16	spooky	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	17	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	One	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
2	1	minute	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	3	you	PRP	O	B-NP	O
2	4	're	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	5	talking	VBG	O	I-VP	O
2	6	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
2	7	longtime	JJ	O	B-NP	O
2	8	character	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	9	actor	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
2	10	Eddie	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
2	11	Carroll	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
2	12	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	Then	RB	O	O	O
3	1	something	NN	O	B-NP	O
3	2	happens	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	3	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
3	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	5	arch	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	6	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	7	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
3	8	eyebrows	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	9	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	His	PP$	O	B-NP	O
4	1	eyes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	2	widen	VBP	O	B-VP	O
4	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	4	and	CC	O	O	O
4	5	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
4	6	face	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	7	takes	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
4	8	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	9	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	10	whimsical	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	11	expression	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	12	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	His	PP$	O	O	O
5	1	head	NN	O	O	O
5	2	cocks	NN	O	O	O
5	3	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
5	4	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
5	5	side	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	6	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	His	PP$	O	B-NP	O
6	1	left	VBN	O	I-NP	O
6	2	hand	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	4	elbow	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	5	supported	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	6	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	7	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	8	right	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	9	hand	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	11	caresses	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
6	12	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
6	13	chin	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	14	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	And	CC	O	O	O
7	1	before	IN	O	O	O
7	2	you	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	3	sits	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	4	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
7	5	iQ	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	6	!	NN	O	I-NP	O
7	7	&	CC	O	I-NP	O
7	8	LR	NNP	O	I-NP	O
7	9	;	:	O	O	O
