0	0	1998-09-21	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	1	15	CD	O	O	B-Num
0	2	:	:	O	O	I-Num
0	3	02	CD	O	B-NP	I-Num
0	4	PENTAGON	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
0	5	UPDATES	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	6	TRAINING	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	7	MANUAL	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
0	8	TO	TO	O	B-PP	I-Org
0	9	INCLUDE	NNP	O	O	I-Org
0	10	URANIUM	NNP	O	O	I-Org
0	11	DANGER	NNP	O	O	I-Org

1	0	ARLINGTON	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
1	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	2	Va.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocStat
1	3	_	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	4	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	5	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	6	move	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	7	applauded	VBD	O	B-VP	O
1	8	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	9	Gulf	NNP	O	B-NP	O
1	10	War	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Event
1	11	veterans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
1	13	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	14	Defense	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
1	15	Department	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
1	16	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
1	17	announced	VBN	O	I-VP	O
1	18	plans	NNS	O	B-NP	O
1	19	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
1	20	add	VB	O	I-VP	O
1	21	information	NN	O	B-NP	O
1	22	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	24	hazards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	25	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	26	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
1	27	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	28	explosions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	29	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
1	30	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	31	manual	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	32	issued	VBN	O	B-VP	O
1	33	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
1	34	all	DT	O	B-NP	O
1	35	soldiers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
1	36	during	IN	O	B-PP	O
1	37	basic	JJ	O	B-NP	O
1	38	training	NN	O	I-NP	O
1	39	.	.	O	O	O

2	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	1	book	NN	O	I-NP	B-Book
2	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	3	formally	RB	O	B-VP	O
2	4	known	VBN	O	I-VP	O
2	5	as	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	7	Common	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Org
2	8	Tasks	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	9	Training	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
2	10	or	CC	O	O	O
2	11	CTT	NNP	O	O	O
2	12	manual	JJ	O	O	O
2	13	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	14	lists	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
2	15	about	IN	O	B-NP	O
2	16	40	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
2	17	duties	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	18	soldiers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
2	19	must	MD	O	B-VP	O
2	20	master	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	21	_	NN	O	B-NP	O
2	22	how	WRB	O	O	O
2	23	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
2	24	dig	VB	O	I-VP	O
2	25	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	26	foxhole	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	28	read	VBD	O	B-VP	O
2	29	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
2	30	compass	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	32	administer	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	33	first	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Num
2	34	aid	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	35	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
2	36	and	CC	O	O	O
2	37	survive	VBP	O	B-VP	O
2	38	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
2	39	hot	JJ	O	B-NP	O
2	40	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
2	41	cold	JJ	O	I-NP	O
2	42	weather	NN	O	I-NP	O
2	43	.	.	O	O	O

3	0	When	WRB	O	O	O
3	1	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	2	revised	VBN	O	I-NP	O
3	3	manual	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	4	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	5	issued	VBN	O	I-VP	O
3	6	later	RB	O	O	O
3	7	this	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	8	year	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	9	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	10	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	11	also	RB	O	O	O
3	12	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
3	13	tell	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	14	soldiers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
3	15	how	WRB	O	O	O
3	16	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
3	17	protect	VB	O	I-VP	O
3	18	themselves	PRP	O	B-NP	O
3	19	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	20	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	21	hazards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
3	22	linked	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	23	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
3	24	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
3	25	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	26	ammunition	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	27	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	28	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
3	29	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	30	made	VBN	O	I-VP	O
3	31	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	32	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	33	heavy	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	34	metal	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	35	that	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	36	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	37	radioactive	JJ	O	O	O
3	38	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	39	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
3	40	Lt.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	41	Col.	NNP	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
3	42	Charles	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
3	43	Kelsey	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
3	44	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	45	who	WP	O	B-NP	O
3	46	serves	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
3	47	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	48	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	49	faculty	NN	O	I-NP	O
3	50	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	51	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
3	52	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
3	53	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
3	54	medical	JJ	O	I-NP	O
3	55	school	NN	O	I-NP	B-OrgUniv
3	56	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
3	57	Bethesda	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
3	58	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
3	59	Md	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Loc
3	60	.	.	O	O	O

4	0	During	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	1	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	2	interview	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	3	Saturday	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
4	4	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	6	third	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
4	7	annual	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	8	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
4	9	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
4	10	Veterans	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
4	11	'	POS	O	B-NP	O
4	12	Illnesses	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Peop
4	13	Conference	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
4	14	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
4	15	Kelsey	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
4	16	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
4	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	18	new	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	19	manual	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	20	will	MD	O	B-VP	O
4	21	address	VB	O	I-VP	O
4	22	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
4	23	hazards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	24	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
4	25	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
4	26	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
4	27	and	CC	O	O	O
4	28	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
4	29	radioactive	JJ	O	I-NP	O
4	30	substances	NNS	O	I-NP	O
4	31	.	.	O	O	O

5	0	Kelsey	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
5	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	2	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
5	3	hazards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	4	posed	VBN	O	B-VP	O
5	5	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	6	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
5	7	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	8	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
5	9	``	``	O	O	O
5	10	pretty	RB	O	O	O
5	11	minor	JJ	O	O	O
5	12	''	''	O	O	O
5	13	compared	VBN	O	B-VP	O
5	14	with	IN	O	B-PP	O
5	15	other	JJ	O	B-NP	O
5	16	battlefield	NN	O	I-NP	O
5	17	dangers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
5	18	.	.	O	O	O

6	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	1	depleted-uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	2	ammunition	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	3	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	4	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
6	5	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	6	fired	VBN	O	I-VP	O
6	7	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	8	U.S.	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
6	9	tanks	NNS	O	I-NP	O
6	10	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
6	11	aircraft	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
6	13	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
6	14	used	VBN	O	I-VP	O
6	15	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	16	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	17	first	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
6	18	time	NN	O	I-NP	O
6	19	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	20	combat	NN	O	B-NP	O
6	21	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
6	22	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
6	23	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
6	24	.	.	O	O	O

7	0	It	PRP	O	B-NP	O
7	1	ignites	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
7	2	on	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	3	impact	NN	O	B-NP	O
7	4	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
7	5	blasts	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	6	holes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
7	7	through	IN	O	B-PP	O
7	8	tanks	NNS	O	B-NP	O
7	9	.	.	O	O	O

8	0	Many	JJ	O	B-NP	O
8	1	nations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	2	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
8	3	since	IN	O	O	O
8	4	added	VBD	O	B-VP	O
8	5	it	PRP	O	B-NP	O
8	6	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
8	7	their	PP$	O	B-NP	O
8	8	arsenals	NNS	O	I-NP	O
8	9	.	.	O	O	O

9	0	Paul	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
9	1	Sullivan	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
9	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	3	executive	JJ	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
9	4	director	NN	O	I-NP	B-ProfTitle
9	5	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
9	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	7	national	JJ	O	I-NP	O
9	8	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
9	9	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	10	Resource	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	11	Center	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
9	12	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	13	which	WDT	O	B-NP	O
9	14	sponsored	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	16	conference	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	17	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
9	18	hailed	VBD	O	B-VP	O
9	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	20	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
9	21	's	POS	O	B-NP	O
9	22	move	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	23	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
9	24	update	VB	O	I-VP	O
9	25	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
9	26	manual	NN	O	I-NP	O
9	27	.	.	O	O	O

10	0	In	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	1	recent	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	2	years	NNS	O	I-NP	B-Date
10	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	4	group	NN	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
10	5	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
10	6	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	7	coalition	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	9	veterans-rights	JJ	O	B-NP	O
10	10	organizations	NNS	O	I-NP	O
10	11	across	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	12	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	13	country	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	14	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
10	15	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
10	16	pressuring	VBG	O	I-VP	O
10	17	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	18	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
10	19	to	TO	O	B-VP	O
10	20	train	VB	O	I-VP	O
10	21	soldiers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
10	22	about	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	23	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
10	24	hazards	NNS	O	I-NP	O
10	25	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
10	26	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
10	27	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	28	exposure	NN	O	I-NP	O
10	29	.	.	O	O	O

11	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
11	1	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
11	2	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	3	Resource	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	4	Center	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	5	also	RB	O	O	O
11	6	advocates	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
11	7	medical	JJ	O	B-NP	O
11	8	care	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	9	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
11	10	compensation	NN	O	I-NP	O
11	11	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
11	12	Gulf	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
11	13	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
11	14	veterans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	15	and	CC	O	O	O
11	16	their	PP$	O	B-NP	O
11	17	families	NNS	O	I-NP	O
11	18	.	.	O	O	O

12	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	1	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
12	2	has	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
12	3	admitted	VBN	O	I-VP	O
12	4	that	IN	O	O	O
12	5	soldiers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
12	6	sent	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	7	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
12	8	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	9	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	O
12	10	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
12	11	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
12	12	told	VBN	O	I-VP	O
12	13	that	DT	O	O	O
12	14	inhaling	VBG	O	O	O
12	15	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	16	ingesting	VBG	O	O	O
12	17	or	CC	O	O	O
12	18	absorbing	VBG	O	B-VP	O
12	19	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	20	hazardous	JJ	O	I-NP	O
12	21	residue	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	22	created	VBN	O	B-VP	O
12	23	by	IN	O	B-PP	O
12	24	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
12	25	depleted	VBN	O	I-NP	O
12	26	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	27	explosion	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	28	could	MD	O	B-VP	O
12	29	cause	VB	O	I-VP	O
12	30	cancer	NN	O	B-NP	B-Medical
12	31	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
12	32	or	CC	O	O	O
12	33	respiratory	JJ	O	B-NP	B-Medical
12	34	COMMA	COMMA	O	I-NP	O
12	35	kidney	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	36	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
12	37	skin	NN	O	I-NP	O
12	38	disorders	NNS	O	I-NP	O
12	39	.	.	O	O	O

13	0	``	``	O	O	O
13	1	We	PRP	O	B-NP	O
13	2	want	VBP	O	B-VP	O
13	3	to	TO	O	I-VP	O
13	4	learn	VB	O	I-VP	O
13	5	from	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	6	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	7	mistakes	NNS	O	I-NP	O
13	8	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
13	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
13	10	pastCOMMA	NN	O	I-NP	O
13	11	''	''	O	O	O
13	12	Sullivan	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
13	13	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
13	14	.	.	O	O	O

14	0	Now	RB	O	O	O
14	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
14	2	many	JJ	O	B-NP	O
14	3	veterans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
14	4	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
14	5	fighting	VBG	O	I-VP	B-Sport
14	6	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	7	medical	JJ	O	B-NP	O
14	8	care	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	9	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
14	10	compensation	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	11	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
14	12	ailments	NNS	O	B-NP	O
14	13	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
14	14	believe	VBP	O	B-VP	O
14	15	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
14	16	linked	VBN	O	I-VP	O
14	17	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
14	18	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
14	19	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	20	exposure	NN	O	I-NP	O
14	21	.	.	O	O	O

15	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
15	1	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
15	2	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
15	3	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	4	January	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Date
15	5	that	IN	O	O	O
15	6	thousands	NNS	O	B-NP	B-Num
15	7	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
15	8	soldiers	NNS	O	B-NP	O
15	9	may	MD	O	B-VP	O
15	10	have	VB	O	I-VP	O
15	11	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
15	12	exposed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
15	13	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
15	14	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
15	15	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
15	16	.	.	O	O	O

16	0	Veterans	NNS	O	B-NP	O
16	1	groups	NNS	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
16	2	have	VBP	O	B-VP	O
16	3	said	VBD	O	I-VP	O
16	4	they	PRP	O	B-NP	O
16	5	believe	VBP	O	B-VP	O
16	6	as	RB	O	B-NP	O
16	7	many	JJ	O	I-NP	O
16	8	as	IN	O	I-NP	O
16	9	400COMMA000	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
16	10	soldiers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
16	11	may	MD	O	B-VP	O
16	12	have	VB	O	I-VP	O
16	13	been	VBN	O	I-VP	O
16	14	exposed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
16	15	.	.	O	O	O

17	0	The	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	1	explosions	NNS	O	I-NP	O
17	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
17	3	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	4	Pentagon	NNP	O	I-NP	B-OrgCorp
17	5	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
17	6	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
17	7	created	VBD	O	B-VP	O
17	8	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
17	9	estimated	VBD	O	I-NP	O
17	10	630COMMA000	CD	O	I-NP	B-Num
17	11	pounds	NNS	O	I-NP	B-NumUnit
17	12	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
17	13	depleted	VBN	O	B-NP	O
17	14	uranium	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	15	dust	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	16	and	CC	O	I-NP	O
17	17	debris	NN	O	I-NP	O
17	18	.	.	O	O	O

18	0	Anthony	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
18	1	Hardie	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Peop
18	2	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
18	3	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	4	30-year-old	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Num
18	5	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
18	6	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
18	7	veteran	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	8	attending	VBG	O	B-VP	O
18	9	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	10	conference	NN	O	I-NP	O
18	11	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
18	12	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	13	depleted	VBN	O	O	O
18	14	uranium	NN	O	B-NP	O
18	15	was	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	16	one	CD	O	B-NP	B-Num
18	17	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	18	many	JJ	O	B-NP	O
18	19	toxic	JJ	O	I-NP	B-Medical
18	20	substances	NNS	O	I-NP	O
18	21	soldiers	NNS	O	I-NP	O
18	22	were	VBD	O	B-VP	O
18	23	exposed	VBN	O	I-VP	O
18	24	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
18	25	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
18	26	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
18	27	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
18	28	.	.	O	O	O

19	0	``	``	O	O	O
19	1	What	WP	O	B-NP	O
19	2	happened	VBD	O	B-VP	O
19	3	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
19	4	us	PRP	O	B-NP	O
19	5	should	MD	O	O	O
19	6	never	RB	O	O	O
19	7	again	RB	O	O	O
19	8	happenCOMMA	NN	O	O	O
19	9	''	''	O	O	O
19	10	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
19	11	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
19	12	.	.	O	O	O

20	0	``	``	O	O	O
20	1	It	PRP	O	B-NP	O
20	2	's	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
20	3	important	JJ	O	O	O
20	4	that	IN	O	O	O
20	5	we	PRP	O	B-NP	O
20	6	protect	VBP	O	B-VP	O
20	7	our	PP$	O	B-NP	O
20	8	current	JJ	O	I-NP	O
20	9	force	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	10	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	11	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	12	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
20	13	and	CC	O	B-PP	O
20	14	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
20	15	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
20	16	service	NN	O	I-NP	O
20	17	.	.	O	O	O
20	18	''	''	O	O	O

21	0	Hardie	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
21	1	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
21	2	who	WP	O	B-NP	O
21	3	served	VBD	O	B-VP	O
21	4	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	5	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	6	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
21	7	and	CC	O	B-PP	O
21	8	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	9	Somalia	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocCoun
21	10	COMMA	COMMA	O	O	O
21	11	is	VBZ	O	B-VP	O
21	12	president	NN	O	B-NP	B-ProfTitle
21	13	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	14	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
21	15	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
21	16	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
21	17	Veterans	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
21	18	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
21	19	Wisconsin	NNP	O	B-NP	B-LocStat
21	20	.	.	O	O	O

22	0	Hardie	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Peop
22	1	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
22	2	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
22	3	became	VBD	O	B-VP	O
22	4	an	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	5	advocate	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	6	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	7	Gulf	NNP	O	B-NP	B-Org
22	8	War	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
22	9	veterans	NNS	O	I-NP	O
22	10	out	IN	O	O	O
22	11	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	12	necessity	NN	O	B-NP	O
22	13	when	WRB	O	O	O
22	14	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
22	15	could	MD	O	B-VP	O
22	16	not	RB	O	I-VP	O
22	17	get	VB	O	I-VP	O
22	18	medical	JJ	O	B-NP	O
22	19	care	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	20	at	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	21	a	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	22	Veterans	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Org
22	23	Administration	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
22	24	Hospital	NNP	O	I-NP	I-Org
22	25	for	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	26	illnesses	NNS	O	B-NP	O
22	27	he	PRP	O	B-NP	O
22	28	said	VBD	O	B-VP	O
22	29	are	VBP	O	B-VP	O
22	30	linked	VBN	O	I-VP	O
22	31	to	TO	O	B-PP	O
22	32	his	PP$	O	B-NP	O
22	33	tour	NN	O	I-NP	O
22	34	of	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	35	duty	NN	O	B-NP	O
22	36	in	IN	O	B-PP	O
22	37	the	DT	O	B-NP	O
22	38	Gulf	NNP	O	I-NP	B-Loc
22	39	.	.	O	O	O
